<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about Envelope Included)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/envelope-included.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: David Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/2015/02/21/from-david-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-and-family/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2624" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09143254_0485.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09143254_0485" width="2780" height="2384"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2625" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09144158_0486.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09144158_0486" width="2815" height="2379"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2626" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09150136_0490.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09150136_0490" width="1484" height="1517"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2627" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09145436_0489.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09145436_0489" width="1472" height="1496"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2628" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09165097_0494.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09165097_0494" width="1487" height="2242"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2629" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09164279_0493.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09164279_0493" width="1480" height="2223"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2630" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150221_09151029_0492.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150221_09151029_0492" width="1430" height="916"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: David Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Pearl, Illinois on May 11, 1886&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Nettie Knox
Sidney - Iowa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pearl May 8, 1886
Dear Nettie, Annie and Family,
Your letter of the 5th received and was glad to hear from you to know of you being all well as this leaves us. I see by your letter and also from Willie's that you are having lots of rain. We are having fine weather here now, not one day since Easter to present plowing or work of dig kind. We had two heavy rains but both came in the night so it did not stop work in the least. Some farmers are done planting. Most about 1/2 done - the corn is coming up fine that is planted and what is looking fine, filled knee height, and fine looking. Fruit is promising all. Only peaches, which are winter killed. Gardens and garden truck look fine. We are having plenty of lettuce and onions coming in now and has been for 8 to 10 days ago. Some growing potatoes look fine 3 to 4 inches high. I do not think that I ever saw such grass or foliage on the trees at this time of year before. We are having delightful weather, as fine as you could wish and even better. The river is falling fast, the water will soon be off the low bottom. Some are now commencing to fill up the bottom, and think they are going to make good crops yet. I have not saw Smith or any of them since I wrote you I learn he is coping in the bottom. As usual he sent me word lately to get him if I could. A bush of broom corn left but I could not get it and sent him word. Lizzie Johnson is still here. Your Ma, Maggie, and her has lots to do. They have a girl called Kate Meginis now for a week helping while they are cleaning house. She is not an expert but does the best she can. Johnie is working on the section with Honan and doing very well. Horan think there never was such a fellow as he is. Still he has to work as other do. I had a letter from Willie same day I got yours. He gave me a full detail of your parties, said he was expecting you over Friday, to stay a day or two. Your Ma is at a loss to know why. You folks are not ready, or could say when you can start or intend to, of course I hate to say any word about your coming. Least Annie does not want too (or cannot make it commence to do so, without great inconvenience.) Hence I am loathe to insist, but it seems to me that the folks, their ought to be getting tired of your lengthy visit. It seems to me that I would not make the folks twice glad, once to see you come and once to see you leave. I do not know that this is the case, but it seems to me you ought to ask sometime.
May 10 I will finish
I went yesterday with Lew Shoustien to visit his folks at Belleview, has a nice time and a pleasant drive, and found Lewis pretty well fixed at home. Has nice property if he had it somewhere to be profitable, but it is like property in Monteguma or Florence , the day has past for such places. I have just got my commission from the governor for Police Magistrate, again, as I was reelected on last election after a big fight - made here by some miracle. Your Ma, Maggie, and Lizzie is having lots to do the last week or so. They have been cleaning house. They had for the last 2 weeks a girl named Kate Meginis helping. She has not much get up about her. We have the house pretty well filled but they keep coming and going, some 5 left today, but there may be 5 or 6 more wanting their place, in a day or two. You must say to Lucy that George is keeping his pants buttoned up and his face washed every day. Our short legged boy is still training so J.W. has better look a little better if he earns that candy.
Yours,
D.Knox&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also in letter:
Dear Annie, G.R., and children,
I drop this note there by Nettie's letter. I started to write you folks Saturday but failed to finish. I am not doing much but I am called away by someone every two or three minutes. I write this to say that we are somewhat disappointed and sorry that you seem to be so preoccupied with work so it is somewhat uncertain where you can make a start. Don't think that we are mad or offended at you, we do not want you to do anything to discontent yourself, or that would be a hardship to you, or any of you, of course we would like to see you all and all. But if there is conflicting elements in the way, so as to be a hardship to you we cannot insist, but if you cannot come I think it would be better for Nettie to come as her  lengthy visit must be getting tiresome to you folks. Besides her Ma could find lots for her to do if at home that would be a great help to het as she is pretty well worn out, we had no idea that she would have stayed over half the time she has stayed. But we are all satisfied, supposing you were going to come with her. We are having very fine weather and all things looking fine. We are having lots of garden vegetables such as onions and lettuce, for some 8 or 10 despots. No late word from Izora or folks. All were all at last report. The water is going down nicely, likely will give no more trouble. Tell Bop. that Nettie and Lucy must give him more room, for his back and tell him to grow big so as to whip this boys here when he does come. Of course Lucy is now quite a little lady, so I am fixing up a nice little handkerchief for her when she comes.
Give my best respects to all and believe that I am as ever your Pa
David Knox
Write soon
Smith was here today. All well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also in letter:
For Lucy and Johnie -
Dear children,
As I did not get Nettie's letter ready tamale yesterday. I will write you a little letter of your own. I will say to you if your Ma do not bring you down here pretty soon, I will send you a ticket so you can come yourself. Be sure you give your Ma no peace till she comes, I am afraid that Lucy will be so big that she will not know her Grand-Pa and the probability is I might not know you and I doubt whether I would know J.W. at all. Still I kind of think I would know you both. At any rate, I do not want you to be much longer coming least you all get out of my knowledges. Oh, Johnie you ought to see a nice little colt I have got for you to ride when you come, and you can loan it to Sister Lucy to ride once in a while. I know Lucy can borrow her Aunt Maggie's saddle, then she can ride about with George of course, Johnie will be boss of the colt, so Lucy will have to talk up her claim to J.W. but I think we can arrange it when you come. You will need a riding whip too. You may bet we will have a good time. You must write me what you think about it so I will have all fixed up when you get here. Love to you from your Grand-Pa.
David Knox&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: David Knox</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/2015/02/21/from-david-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-and-family/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2015 19:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Betty Tilley, To: Amelua J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1941/06/30/from-betty-tilley-to-amelua-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2808" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_10362360_0662.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_10362360_0662" width="2443" height="3022"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2810" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1941/06/postcard-2014-20150321_10364247_0666.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_10364247_0666" width="1787" height="1081"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2811" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1941/06/postcard-2014-20150321_10363536_0665.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_10363536_0665" width="1737" height="1069"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Betty Tilley, To:  Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Topeka, Kansas on June 30, 1941&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins
725 Waverly Route 5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. H.W. Tilley
Hotel Paumee
Merik Platte, Nebraska&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Aunt Millie,
We are in a hurry, ready to leave Topeka for Merik Platte Nebraska, Hotel Paumee. Enclosed is a letter Maifer wrote you some time ago. It is almost impossible for her to write as her vision is so bad. She can not read at all. Maifer is going to Merik Platte with me. Shall write you again when hot in such a rush to leave town. Have a four hundred mile drive ahead of us. We hope you are feeling better dear. I am awfully bust all the time. Together with caring for Maifer and this big house it is so much for me. We are all pretty well however. Hope to hear from you, maybe you know some one who will send us a card to The Paumee Htel at Merik Platte Nebraska.
Love from both of us.
Your devoted niece
Betty
(Mrs. H.W. Tilley)&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Betty Ann Tilley</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1941/06/30/from-betty-tilley-to-amelua-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 1941 16:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Lucila, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1936/04/14/from-lucila-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2814" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11343699_0668.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11343699_0668" width="1498" height="2244"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2815" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11342653_0667.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11342653_0667" width="1480" height="2215"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2816" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11350406_0670.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11350406_0670" width="1496" height="2241"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2817" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11353436_0672.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11353436_0672" width="1807" height="1086"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2818" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11352647_0671.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11352647_0671" width="1766" height="1083"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Lucila, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Phoenix, Arizona on April 14, 1936&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;725 Waverly St. R-5&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If not called for in 30 Days
Return it to Miss Nellie
Yorks Gem Dr
Phoenix, Arizona&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix, Ariz
April 12, 1936
Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins
Dear Mother,
As I have time I thought I would write you a few lines. Hoping my letter will find well. I am all right. How is it down there in Ohio? You You are all having some awful floods from what I seen in papers and what I been told. So I thought I would write to see if you are still alive. I hope that you dont get in those awful floods. We are beginning to have awful hot weather. I like Arizona - that is the weather here, but in summer it gets awful hot here. I feel it here more than I did any place I lived. I sure love to go back to Calif and go to Hollywood. I know all the movie stars. When is you birthday Mother? O yes have you heard anything about my kids.
Well mother I must close for this time, as I have one more letter to write. I remember the good times we used to have together. Then I got to go to town and I mail this on my way to town. I sure love to hear from my kids.
Have you every read that letter from my daughter she write to you.
Well good mother again I say good bye with love to you till I hear from you again will writte me next time.
Your daughter
Lucia&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Lucila</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1936/04/14/from-lucila-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 1936 17:35:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Inez and Grover, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1932/11/01/from-inez-and-grover-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140602_18542817_0461.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1084" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140602_18542817_0461.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140602_18542817_0461" width="1479" height="989"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140602_18541401_0460.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1085" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140602_18541401_0460.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140602_18541401_0460" width="1448" height="979"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1932/11/postcard-2014-20140602_19134945_0471.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1096" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1932/11/postcard-2014-20140602_19134945_0471.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140602_19134945_0471" width="1529" height="1007"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Inez and Grover, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on November 11, 1932&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mailing Address:
Mrs. Nett Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Return Address:
1901 S. Lawrence
Wichita, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Aunt Nett,
Just a few lines to thank you for your nice letter which we recieved some time ago. We are getting along nicely but it is sure lonely without my dear Mother. I don't think I'll ever get over missing her. Ruby has been so loyal to use. I don't know what we would have done without here. G.C. worked at the elections board yesterday and isn't home yet this a.m. Roosevelt sure went over big. I hope he can do something for us.
We wish you would come out here again this winter and make us a nice visit.
Mae was down for a week or more, fixing up the house on Holyoke. It is for rent again. Write when convenient.
Much Love,
Inez and Grover&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Inez and Grover</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1932/11/01/from-inez-and-grover-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 1932 00:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1930/12/31/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17205403_0241.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-663" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17205403_0241.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17205403_0241" width="2147" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17204221_0240.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-662" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17204221_0240.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17204221_0240" width="2147" height="3011"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17230938_0243.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-664" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17230938_0243.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17230938_0243" width="2147" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17225785_0242.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-665" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17225785_0242.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17225785_0242" width="2153" height="3011"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17243788_0245.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-666" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17243788_0245.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17243788_0245" width="2153" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17242642_0244.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-667" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17242642_0244.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17242642_0244" width="2153" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1930/12/postcard-2014-20140528_18222793_0381.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-860" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1930/12/postcard-2014-20140528_18222793_0381.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140528_18222793_0381" width="2134" height="1178"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on December 31, 1930 Mailed Address: Mrs. E.H. Chandler Pearl, Illinois Return Address: Mrs. Sam Mullholland 421 E. Lewis Wichita, Kansas Wichita, Kansas December 31, 1930 Dearest Mama and Martin Received your letter yesterday also one from Bess saying John was led past with such a bad back. Said he suffered terribly the past two night. I want to write her again today. I've written Grace so maybe I'll get such debts settled before the new year. I was reminded of my position Saturday on account of dill times. He told me I had done marvelously well, etc and if I needed references to tell them to come to him. I was there just a month. I'm not going to look for anything else for we'll be moving soon. The van will go to Fredonia for out things Saturday and Sunday and we'll be in by the 8th. I hope mostly straightened up by that time. It's petty far out on N. Laurence 3701. Gene will be transferred to Central International Mediate for the new semester. That school is real close to the golf course. Sam will bring him back and forth. Sam goes to work on an oil lease for the present out 3 miles starting the 2nd. So, he is lucky to get anything as many as are having let out. Grove not Bob have anything in sight either. Those of our fame;y who have good positions are in luck sure enough. Bess Doesn't write so optimistic either but she doesn't mind any hardships where her family is connected. She surely is big hearted. Her biggest worry is John's sickness and I surely hope he improves soon. Took sick the next day after Christmas she said. Mama you didn't say if you got my box of candy. We mailed it the same time as the letter you received. I hope it wasn't lost. I was surprised about Lucille having another girl. I wonder how Aunt Belle is now? We had cards from Virginia and Dr. I didn't send one to Va. as I didn't get her address and I was too busy to get it. Mother Davis is growing weaker. A.V. [Arthur Vincent] provides a nurse and they have a girl, too. So that is all he can do. He just can't get there often on account of his work. Mother Muir is fine - makes quilts all the time but it costs them plenty to get them quilted. At least $8 a piece and they drive to Sedgewick to take them to a woman who does it for them Gene is raising the roof with his bugle. He likes to practice on it. His vacation lasts until the 4th. Ours up here is the 8th so that gives us 4 days to get our furniture straightened. I'll have to cook with electricity as we'll be out beyond the gas main and water line. But the owner says the improvements will be extended right away. The house is brick and seems to be nice enough. Will tell you more about it after we get in. This house belongs to another concern Sam is interested in and the partner seems  very anxious for us to get in and look after things. The advantage in going there is the rental is free and that means a lot at preset. You surely have had some game, haven't you? I'd like to eat rabbit with you. Gene's out in the sun - bareheaded just tearing around on his roller skates. It is so pretty out. We had the one snow and the river was full of ice blocks at that time but it has been so mild for a week. I surely hope it will remain mild for the most of the winter and for your sake I hope you don't have such cold weather if you have to be in Pearl. That house is too hard for you to manage through the winter and I wish I could help you, but it will be rather difficult for me too so I'll be glad when spring comes. I surely hope Martin is better by now. Tell him he's better drop us a line. There isn't very much to write since I last wrote. Wish I had a birthday presently for you - but wishes are not very substantial. Anyway I hope you keep real will till your next birthday and hope to see you before your next. Love to both of you, Ruby, Sam, and Gene</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland</category><category>Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1930/12/31/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1930 23:13:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1929/02/19/from-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1524" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16212047_0695.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16212047_0695" width="2141" height="3035"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1525" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16210886_0694.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16210886_0694" width="2123" height="3029"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1526" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16223107_0697.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16223107_0697" width="2141" height="1151"&gt;From: Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Dunlap, Iowa on February 19, 1929
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. E.H. Chandler
937 Jackson
Fredonia, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dunlap, Iowa
Feb. 19, 1929
Dearest Mama and Everyone,
Received your letter, Mama, some 3 or 4 days ago, and decided not to let my answer be delayed as long as it was before. Not much news to write, but will try to fill out a page anyway. Here it is, almost the last of this month, and we are having sub zero weather yet. It is now 8:00 PM and the mercury stands at 5 degrees below zero. The warmest part of the day was noon, and it was 6 degrees above then. Our coldest day, so far, has been 30 degrees below. I had my ears slightly frostbitten then but all traces of it has disappeared now. That is the only time I've ever had any part of my anatomy frost-bitten, and I hope it is the last. It isn't pleasant at all. We got a letter from Mart the other day, Oh no, it was from Lou and she said Mart is working extra up in Wisconsin, for the A.P. She also wrote that Mart had abstained from partaking of alcoholic beverages since Thanksgiving which was mighty good news for all of us, and I know that yo will be glad to hear it too, if you haven't hear before this. I sincerely hope he sticks to it. He said that he hadn't the least appetite for it, and was off of it. I can hardly read my own writing, due perhaps, to my aversion to writing letters.
I'd sure love to see Gene, and his parents. He must be getting to be a pretty fair musician, and would love to hear him perform. Will close for now, answer soon.
Love,
Knox&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Knox</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1929/02/19/from-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 1929 22:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Rosa and Fred, To: John Roush</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1927/11/17/from-rosa-and-fred-to-john-roush/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1519" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16050720_0691.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16050720_0691" width="3419" height="2015"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1520" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16045501_0690.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16045501_0690" width="3419" height="2027"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1521" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16060852_0693.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16060852_0693" width="1793" height="1049"&gt;From: Rosa and Fred, To: John Roush
Mailed From: Dunlap, Iowa on November 17, 1927
&lt;p&gt;Mr. John Roush
Pearl, Ill
c/o Mrs. Chandler&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday P.M.
Dear Folks,
Just got your card. Are sure sorry you were so unfortunate as to get sick there. Hope you are better by now. We would elite to send you our fur coat down for you to wear home. If you will let us low if it will be ample time for it to get there. Am sorry Mr. Chandler had to be taken from you all but it seems like that is our lot - sooner or later to pass on into the life beyond. We have the fresh pork in the cooler so you need not worry over it. Let Jap know when you are going to be in Quincy and they can be on the lookout for you. He is very anxious to see you too. We are all well. Things going about the same. Will close &amp;amp; get this mailed.
Lots of love and best wishes to all and extend my sympathy to your mother, Bess to.
From Rosa &amp;amp; Fred&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Rosa and Fred</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: John Roush</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1927/11/17/from-rosa-and-fred-to-john-roush/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 1927 22:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: N.J. Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1927/06/02/from-n-j-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1531" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140630_09400213_0699.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140630_09400213_0699" width="2483" height="3191"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1532" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140630_09394996_0698.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140630_09394996_0698" width="2483" height="3185"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1533" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140630_09404850_0701.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140630_09404850_0701" width="1853" height="1061"&gt;From: N. J. Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: White Hall, Ill. on June 3, 1927
&lt;p&gt;Miss E. H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 5 Days Return to
Greene County Medical Society
White Hall, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sister &amp;amp; family!
Yours received and glad to hear from you and to know all are well. Very sorry indeed to hear of sister Annie's illness. I am guessing her trouble to be Bronchitis- instead of Pneumonia, or Broner's - Pneumonia as it is the wrong time of year for Pneumonia. Bronchitis is trouble enough. I hope when you hear again she will be better. Ruby sure did make some time, that was going some.Loren and he girls will have a great time on their trip to Dunlop and return and when two or more traveling over-land on a trip of like distance it is a great saving of time and expense to go prepared to camp. Mr. &amp;amp; Mrs. J.C. Spencer drove to California last year, was in a home here, and only don't know whether they were alone or not, think they were, but they camped all the way and enjoyed it, saw so much of the county. The general health during winter and to present time has been good, although quite a number of old chronic cases ave passed away o late. Mr. Fox has been very busy some days with calls near towns and here would have 3 on hand in one day. I don't believe his auto hearse was on to Pearl lately, that may have been - it goes to Jacksonville, Manedesto, Roadhouse, and Carrollton frequently. Russell is helping him and has done so on Saturday or other times when not engaged at school - he expects to go to college this fall. Lucile and Brausford drover here from Sadores on Monday for the commencement, they returned Wednesday afternoon today, Kenneth with them. We miss him so much. He will go to 8th grade in Junior High next year. I would proved some way of securely marking plain letters, all clothes - even shoes you take to Annie. They are stolen and would not be so liable to be taken when marked. That last two patients by death, recently, Mrs. Griswalk and Mrs. Staples. The latter was a large woman and as strong as an ox. Bright's disease with cancer of stomach is back. I know Dr. Lucas, now at the State Institution, he supervised me at Manchester, lost his wife last year by death. I had known her long before I had met him. She was reared near Manchester. Since his wife died, he said it was "just a little more than a dog's life in general practice" sleeping at one place and eating at another. He received appointment to Jacksonville and immediately pulled out. He comes to Manchester on Saturdays - principally to collect. I have not been to Jacksonville since last fall - not been any where for some time. I wasn't to go to Jacksonville soon. I must see D. Adams concerning my eyes and have glasses fitted that I can so. I was forced to get a pair here of an optometrist, and they are really doing my eyes an injury. I would be willing to go with you to Jacksonville some time soon, if it is possible I might do more or as much good, if I would go myself - only that you could perhaps have an opportunity to present complaints. When we do go, I could not expect to do other business - as the visit there would take up all of our time. If you want me to go with you, you would have to take your chance on me being in position to go with you when you do come. Practice is rather quiet at present time. I would be glad for you to come at any time. An invitation to Medical Grants at Sidney for tomorrow, but I will not attempt to go.
We will expect to hear from the "kids" today, they left there at 4:30 pm with 150 miles or a little more to dive and at 8:30 it was storming here. With no trouble they should be well on their way between Springfield and Decatin, they would not expect to arrive at Sadonia before midnight. They choose the last hour leaving, because it would be cooler and the eve sun to their backs.
Your Bro,
N.J. Knox
I think Belle and Russell will go latter part of next month. We have our Company Medical School much here on the 10th at the Chaytagun grounds, as a basket pit. Nice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: N.J. Knox</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1927/06/02/from-n-j-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 1927 15:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Russ F. Souers, To: Lucerne Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1925/02/07/from-russ-f-souers-to-lucerne-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1766" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141114_13403127_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141114_13403127_0002" width="1622" height="1090"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1767" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141114_13402369_0001.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141114_13402369_0001" width="1617" height="1083"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1768" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141114_13411734_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141114_13411734_0002" width="2206" height="1501"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1769" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141114_13413129_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141114_13413129_0002" width="2213" height="1502"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1770" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141114_13414103_0004.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141114_13414103_0004" width="2211" height="1522"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1771" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141114_13414503_0006.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141114_13414503_0006" width="2218" height="1527"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Russ F. Souers, To: Lucerne Chandler
Mailed From: Chicago, Illinois on February 7, 1925&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Lucerne Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R.F. Souers
Ass'd Press.
Chicago, Ills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chicago, Ills
Feb 7 1925.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Honey:---
I sure am curious to know why you asked me if I'd love you even though you didn't love me and decided not to marry me. I'm not going to let you decided not to marry me, or at least I'm going to do my damnedest not to. The true answer though, is that I'd still love you. --- But why did you ask me that. Hope it wont turn out that way. I'd sure feel awfully badly about it if it did.
We had a very successful meal at home last night. Mart &amp;amp; I decided to go home and cook a meal in preference to going to the movie show. We had sirloin steak, fried potatoes, macaroni and cheese, green onions, buns and butter, and coffee and pumpkin pie. Sure was a good meal. You should see me wash dishes. I'm getting to be an expert. I had the table all cleared up and washed the dishes in about ten minutes. Freddy wiped 'em. --- I'm practicing so's perhaps, mebbe, I'll wash the dishes for you one in awhile. That's a promise Honey.
The poker game was successful, in a way. I won $22, but loaned out $15 more that I won, so in a way I won, and another way I lost. However, I think its all good. I'll get it sometime. Gosh but I'm tired today, though. That's what I don't like about it. Always feel so tired the next day. Its lots of fun though. The boys crack funny jokes, and we manage to have a pretty good time out of it. Also I'll be able to sleep good tonight.
Guess Mart &amp;amp; I will go McVickers tonight. And get home early and get a good night's sleep. I've got to work tomorrow afternoon. Haven't seen a movie show all week. Ye Gods how I wish you were here to go with me. Honey, again I tell you I miss you like hell.
Did you get the new Motion Picture magazine. Haven't seen the latest issue of the Photoplay, but I'll send it when it comes out. Can you think of any books you'd like to have, or anything else, just let me know, and I'll be tickled to death to get 'em or it for you.
Sure was foggy this owning. The levanted trains went along like snails this morning. All three of us came down to work together and thought sure we'd be late. But we started about fifteen minutes earlier than usual this morning , we wanted to get a heavy breakfast. And the L's were so slow we didn't even have tim e to get a cup of coffee. Just barely managed to get in the office at one minute after nine. It was so foggy you couldn't see ten feet away. Just like old Lunnon.
Guess I'll drop this in the mail box now so's perhaps you'll get it Sunday, if the post office is open.
Wish I was going to see you this evening. Hope you come back soon.
I love you, Honey.
Russ,&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Russ F. Souers</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Lucerne Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1925/02/07/from-russ-f-souers-to-lucerne-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 1925 20:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: William Thomas Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1920/07/05/from-william-thomas-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-and-family/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2454" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150121_15505966_0382.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150121_15505966_0382" width="1482" height="2242"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2455" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150121_15505143_0381.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150121_15505143_0381" width="1474" height="2212"&gt; &lt;img class=" size-full wp-image-2456 alignright" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150121_15572643_0384.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150121_15572643_0384" width="1687" height="1042"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: William Thomas Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Whitehall, Ill. on July 5, 1920&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whitehall, Ill July 4, 1920
Dear Sister and family,
I have since you were here, been making inquiry whenever I could in regard to the "Annex" to the State Hospital. These buildings are for Vocational training of patients that can be trusted or handled outside of the main building. This state and Hospital has gained world wide reputation since taking up this line of training of inmates and has recently attracted leading physicians of other state institutions there to learn the details of this work. The idea is this: to give those that can be trusted the best of environments afforded with something to keep their minds and body employed and with the training and treatment, many of them will soon recover. Dr. Chapin was here yesterday. He speaks very highly of Dr. Hill, and of being a gentleman of the highest type, but his letter to you was a mistaken identity - or he was badly off. I want to go to the Hospital and meet Dr. Hill and would like D. C. or some other physician of acquaintance to go with me.
I believe the Annex is the best for Annie, she has heard of the Annex, and formed a wrong conception of its purposes. Perhaps though after patients that did not know any more of it than she didd and had become biased against it by name, without knowing its real purpose. Mr. and Mrs. Fox, Edith &amp;amp; Mildred drove to Pittsfield Friday, stopped at Milton for minutes. Mr. Fox has business that took him there.
Lucile is home, expect to remain for another week or possibly longer. I am expecting to go to J-Ville soon and will if I have the time to visit the Hospt, but doubt  that invite. I expect to take a patient to Dr. Morbury and other doctors for examination and may be crowded for time at the visit. What has become of John? I used to hear from him once and a while, not for a long time now.
Your Bro,
W.T. Knox&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: William Thomas Knox</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1920/07/05/from-william-thomas-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-and-family/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 1920 22:34:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>