<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about From: Knox)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/from-knox.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1929/02/19/from-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1524" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16212047_0695.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16212047_0695" width="2141" height="3035"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1525" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16210886_0694.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16210886_0694" width="2123" height="3029"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1526" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140626_16223107_0697.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140626_16223107_0697" width="2141" height="1151"&gt;From: Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Dunlap, Iowa on February 19, 1929
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. E.H. Chandler
937 Jackson
Fredonia, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dunlap, Iowa
Feb. 19, 1929
Dearest Mama and Everyone,
Received your letter, Mama, some 3 or 4 days ago, and decided not to let my answer be delayed as long as it was before. Not much news to write, but will try to fill out a page anyway. Here it is, almost the last of this month, and we are having sub zero weather yet. It is now 8:00 PM and the mercury stands at 5 degrees below zero. The warmest part of the day was noon, and it was 6 degrees above then. Our coldest day, so far, has been 30 degrees below. I had my ears slightly frostbitten then but all traces of it has disappeared now. That is the only time I've ever had any part of my anatomy frost-bitten, and I hope it is the last. It isn't pleasant at all. We got a letter from Mart the other day, Oh no, it was from Lou and she said Mart is working extra up in Wisconsin, for the A.P. She also wrote that Mart had abstained from partaking of alcoholic beverages since Thanksgiving which was mighty good news for all of us, and I know that yo will be glad to hear it too, if you haven't hear before this. I sincerely hope he sticks to it. He said that he hadn't the least appetite for it, and was off of it. I can hardly read my own writing, due perhaps, to my aversion to writing letters.
I'd sure love to see Gene, and his parents. He must be getting to be a pretty fair musician, and would love to hear him perform. Will close for now, answer soon.
Love,
Knox&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Knox</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1929/02/19/from-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 1929 22:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1886/03/04/from-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-2/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2589" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150216_17142246_0458.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150216_17142246_0458" width="2827" height="2374"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2590" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150216_17141021_0457.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150216_17141021_0457" width="2796" height="2371"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2591" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150216_17143704_0460.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150216_17143704_0460" width="1487" height="2255"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2592" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150216_17142857_0459.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150216_17142857_0459" width="1482" height="2234"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2593" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150216_17144637_0462.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150216_17144637_0462" width="1552" height="985"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Knox, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Pearl, Illinois on March 4, 1886&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Nettie Knox
Sidney, Ia
Fremont Co&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pearl, Ill. Much. 1st
Dear Sister,
I will now write you a few lines, as I am sitting around doing nothing. Tell Nett I thot all the time that I had written the last time but Liz says I have not so now I will try to let you know that I am still alive. Well "Jimett" Willie says you are flying high, well if you hold your head up I know the end of your nose will be high. Nett I guess you will bring him home with you when you come. I judge from the way you are staying that you are waiting for him to return from college. Well Nett I have had lots of fun this winter and then you know, my Old Gal has been staying here and of course I had a good time. Lizzie R has been at our house almost every day this week and she is to be over today (Sunday) to spend the day. I have been invited back there several times but I haven't gone yet and don't intend to go. She said she was going to quit asking me if I didn't soon come. She asked me to go over home with her the other eve. I went as far as the door and came back, she said she thought I was acting awful smart. Oh say did you get many Valentines? I got some horrible ones. Every one that got any thot I sent them, and so they thot they would pay me back but I never sent but two. Maggie has been gone up to Judy's for fur weeks and is not home yet. She was to be home in side of a week when she first went and Smith was here on Tues. and said he would bring her down next day but they have not come yet. Bu we looked for them today. This is a very blustery day. It is blowing snow and the ground is now white.
Stewart still holds the fort but Lizzie's Ma was down the other day and gave her her orders, but he was here last night. I guess Liz wont pay much attention to her. Ira Hanback is here now. He is keeping saloon for Sink. Sink has had 2 dancers this week but they never amounted to much. I was at one of them and the other I didn't go. The two Lizzie's wouldn't go. Well Nett when are you coming home? You must soon come and don't fail to bring Anne with you. Tell her she must come. Well I close for this time. Hoping you are all well. I guess I'll write a little while I am at it and have lots of time.
Well Nett, Maggie hasn't come today. Pas says I'll have to go after her tomorrow as he is getting awful lonesome without her. Lizzie T is here. She came out 11 o'clock. Nett we had 8 chickens for dinner today. "Euymph Golly" did we (or I) have a good time eating old "Yaller lege." "You'd orter" been here.
Nett one of the men that stays here is very sick. He has the Lung Fever and it is very inconvenient for to take care of him. I suppose you have heard of the slanderous reports on Mol Rose and Lansdon. I guess they are all very true but they denied it. They came near being expelled from school but by Nick Smith's influence they were retained. I did hope for some time that they would get it, but I suppose it is now squashed at last for the time being. Well that os all now. Give Anne, G.R, and Children my best wishes,
Yours Muchly,
K
Lizzie T: says for me to kiss her once for you. Of course I wont object.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Knox</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1886/03/04/from-knox-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-2/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 1886 00:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>