<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about From: Ruby Chandler)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/from-ruby-chandler.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1920/03/15/from-ruby-chandler-to-e-h-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="http://107.170.91.122/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140411_17143146_0001.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-130" src="http://107.170.91.122/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140411_17143146_0001.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140411_17143146_0001" width="1530" height="977"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://107.170.91.122/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140411_17115386_0002.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-129" src="http://107.170.91.122/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140411_17115386_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140411_17115386_0002" width="905" height="1667"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
From: Ruby Chandler, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Wichita Kansas, Union Station on March 15, 1920
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Elijah H. Chandler (Jeanette Knox Chandler)
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday A.M.
Dearest Folk,
Rather slow acknowledging receipt of the little suit. Thanks so much-came when I needed it most. It fit to perfection-as if you'd had him there. He looks so sweet in it. Jean is a good little boy and so bright. In fact, we all idolize him. It is so very long till you'll be coming and I'm so anxious for you to come. Hope this finds you all well. Vinnie leaves here Wednesday I think. Sam left this A.M.
Lovingly,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1920/03/15/from-ruby-chandler-to-e-h-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 1920 23:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/08/02/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-2/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2570" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150211_15541762_0446.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150211_15541762_0446" width="1880" height="2916"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2571" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150211_15540833_0445.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150211_15540833_0445" width="1866" height="2878"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2572" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150211_16143298_0450.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150211_16143298_0450" width="1916" height="2922"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2573" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150211_16142185_0449.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150211_16142185_0449" width="1903" height="2895"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2574" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150211_16012622_0447.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150211_16012622_0447" width="1894" height="2888"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2575" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150211_16013550_0448.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150211_16013550_0448" width="1908" height="2914"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Morrisonville, Illinois on August 2, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. L.E. Gowin
Morrisonville, Ill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday Evening
Aug 2, 1918
Dearest Folks,
Arrived this afternoon at 3 o'clock. Bess and Mae got here at 6:30. We should have gotten here at 8:30 am but the C&amp;amp;A was late, about an hour, and the Frisco had changed time of departure from St. L at 2 pm instead of 2:15 so we missed it by 10 minutes. So we didn't get out of St. L until 8:30 pm.
We ate lunch and as we started to Granite on the McKinley car Bill got on at the same time. He got a short furlough from Paris Island SC. Sam had such a good visit with him. Bill seems so much more talkative and jolly.
We were over there until 6:30 pm but the girls were in St. L shopping so we just did get to see them between the time they got there till the next car. We had had dinner in St. L and by the time we got back and ate supper we just had time to get our train.
A young woman and her baby happened to be on the same pullman and had been visiting at the Legits at Waterford, Ohio where Sam and I visited. When I was talking to her she mentioned having been to Ohio and I told her my husband and I had been there too before we went to visit at Ill and she said "I'll bet you are Mrs. Sam Mulholland" and you can imagine how surprised I was. She was coming to Eldorado, Kas.
(Tues) I didn't get this mailed when my intentions were so good too to write immediately.
It has been murderously hot here. Sunday it was 106 degrees at 2 pm and it was almost unbearably at nights until last night.
It was pretty tough to see him leaving and it will still be hard to get along without him. But I am hoping he gets to stay at Ft. Riley so he wont be so far away. The train was supposed to leave at 6 am yesterday but it was finally 7:30 before the train left. The W.C.T.W. women presented each draftee with a comfort kit - a khaki bag containing a money pouch, an expense book, needles and thread packets and several things so handy. Sam was real proud of his.
I can anyway look forward to his letters and be interested in what I can scrape up to tell him.
I am enclosing a check for Margaret's operation. I wish she could stay there at M-Ville long enough to go to the Springfield Fair and then have Dr. meet you and Margaret about the 14th to have her tonsils and adenoids removed. Will you write to Dr. right away and see if he can manage to go at that time.
Maybe Opal will loan Margaret an extra gown or two for hospital use and I don't know what inconvenience there could be for Mae described Virginia's case so well I know there'll be very little, if any, extra expense. Lucerne can manage the housekeeping while you are in Granite and Maybe Warren can take you and Margaret to the hospital in his car. Maybe its a good plan to have Margaret come to Granite and be there when you and Dr. go down so you all could go right out to the hospital first thing and you'd have no responsibilities regarding the cars or locating the hospital.
I'll surely be relieved for her to start into school without that hinderance to her speech and breathing.
School begins here the 9th. I'm sure Papa can bring the girls to KC and put them on their train for Wichita. Will try to have all arrangements made for them so if they don't get here until  few days before the 9th it will be OK. I guess Papa can have their passes by that time.
We're anxious to hear of Martin, so let us know as soon as you hear.
We have a little ironing to do before we go to Mae's so we have to get busy.
last but not least, we sure did enjoy the buns, and we were glad too to get the yeast since each of us forgot it. Thanks for sending so quickly the things we over looked. Write soon and let us know plans.
Lots of Love,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/08/02/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-2/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 1918 22:16:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Margaret Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1917/12/11/from-ruby-chandler-to-margaret-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18070261_0066.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-328" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18070261_0066.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140421_18070261_0066" width="1535" height="976"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18071028_0067.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-329" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18071028_0067.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140421_18071028_0067" width="971" height="1534"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Margaret Chandler
Mailed From: Morrisonville, Illinois on December 11, 1917&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Margaret Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morrisonville
12-11-'17
Dearest Folks,
I guess we'll get there Saturday noon-sooner if we can. Want to get back Friday if possible. It has been awfully cold the whole week-as I suppose you know. December 24 will be an eventful day. We have been doing a good deal but get up so late Ma keeps the day so short. We've been wondering what you heard from Aunt Annie. Christmas is sure awfully near! Hope everybody is well. Lucille, I got some music you'll like. So you can practice to your heart's content on Sunday. We went to shake last night. Made fudge and popcorn. Grace has a new coat. Pretty!
Love to all,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Margaret Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1917/12/11/from-ruby-chandler-to-margaret-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 1917 00:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1915/01/02/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-3/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1424" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140616_11352293_0626.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140616_11352293_0626" width="1040" height="1481"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1425" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/postcard-2014-20140616_11353093_0627.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140616_11353093_0627" width="1513" height="1036"&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Kansas City, Mo. on January 2, 1915
Picture Info: Hotel Mercer, 12th and McGee, Kansas City, Mo.
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1-1-1915
Dearest One,
Am leaving for Wichita at 10 pm. Will arrive there at 6 am Saturday. Will write real soon. Guess the girls got there on 16. Had a nice time today. They insisted on me staying until tonight. Write.
Love,
R.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1915/01/02/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-3/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 1915 17:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1912/10/23/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1667" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15501864_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15501864_0002" width="1873" height="2870"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1668" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15500980_0001.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15500980_0001" width="1868" height="2859"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1669" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15502305_0004.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15502305_0004" width="1860" height="2865"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1670" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15501963_0003.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15501963_0003" width="1836" height="2861"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1671" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15510012_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15510012_0002" width="1866" height="2873"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1672" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15505107_0001.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15505107_0001" width="1860" height="2856"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1677" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15511030_00041.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15511030_0004" width="1879" height="2867"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1674" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15510215_0003.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15510215_0003" width="1862" height="2858"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1675" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15511554_0006.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15511554_0006" width="1877" height="2879"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1676" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/postcard-2014-20140827_15511125_0005.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140827_15511125_0005" width="1884" height="2868"&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on October 23, 1912
&lt;p&gt;Wichita, Kansas October 23, '12
Dearest Papa, Mamma, and All:
We received the children's and Papa's letters yesterday, Mamma's registered and Bess' letters today so I feel especially good tonight.
I was awfully glad to get the $15.00 for Martin's suit. Will order it Saturday, then he'll get it in a week. After this month thought I will have gotten a good start and wont be so hard pressed for extra coin. We'll get a pay day a few days earlier this month on account of the Topeka trip. Say Papa I wish you'd order it right away for Ill need it the 6th and thats a short time off. order it Via Rock Island as a special is chartered for the benefit of Wichita teachers and promises to get us there in about 14 and a half hours.
I was glad Bess sent that music. I have those two you mentioned but can't locate the song book. Will tell you later what I do and what happens.
Bess, I was rather depending on you ordering my hat thru Edna, since you were going to pay me a little on my coat than $5.00. But if you can't share it, I can wait until I get my next pay and get it here the day before I go to Topeka for I can't get it right now.
Form the way your letters read it seemed you didn't get my last one for in it I asked about my hat and told you what I wanted also told Mamma on back of envelope it was ok about bed trade.
If you can't order hat thru Edna I'll first get a sailor for I'd have to pay a sum for beaver and trim it like I want it. Ethyl and I rented a piano and it was moved in last Sat. so I feel so much more at home. I was first crazy about before I got it. I sure will put in the time. Martin learned to play "Rock of Ages" clear thru with both hands. He's awfully proud of it. ha! He's onto Mae's now. I had to go to Teacher's Association and a dinner afterwards so he went out there. I had him go to a "Delicatessen" right near us, for his supper and go out there afterwards. I haven't seen her since Sunday but called her up this noon and she said she'd be down after school tomorrow. I did quite a washing last night and ironed this a.m. before I went to school so as to be ready for that down tonight. I wore my white veil and a tight red low made from the ribbon on my summer hat, put it right in the back. It looked good. I had several compliments. You know, my veil dress split in 3 or 4 places and I took it to Boston Store and showed them and they gave me $2.50 due bill for material. So I got a wide insertion and set it in which also lengthened it just enough. I'm quite proud of my handiwork. I still have $1.00 of that left. Not in money but due - bill. It will come in handy sometime.
I am going to a show this week and wear my light blue dress. Ethyl had a fit over it. I agent been ad it on yet. I will be the first show I have seen, not even the princess. Sam is join got take me to Forum Friday night.
I'm glad Grace got her a traveling bag. One needs it so often. Mine will come in handy at Topeka. Say, I fixed my blue dress up dandy so I can wear it all winter. I cleaned it and pressed it and put the waist back on so it looks most as good as new. I'll clean my lavender so I can take both to the convention.
Say, I have got a peachy coat. It's a mixture and has big lapels of broadcloth. It's as swell as any I've seen. It's the bicle cloth, pretty rough mostly black, so a black hat will go well with it. Bess did you get your grey beaver trimmed with pink. I saw one down town, and it would be so pretty for you.
Grace are you wearing your suit or your cast winter coat? You didn't mention so I wondered. Your blue suit was pretty on you.
The children's letters were so cute. I can read them over and over and laugh every time. It sure tickles Martin to hear what Knox says. He says "Don't you wish we had him here." I have thought so often how much good it would do one of the little girls here with we while they were out of school so long. I want them to have music so bad. After awhile I'm going to ave Martin play. He wants to so bad and it seems easy for him.
I forgot to tell you how I paid for my coat. Why since I'm a teacher I can run a bill, so whatever is absolutely necessary I can get there anytime. It came in handy for I needed it so bad when I got my dresses, I still wear my suit lots but its so hard to keep my waist ironed. I had them rough dried at the Steam Laundry also sheets, pillow cases and table cloths and Martin's collars, came to $0.47. I'm going to have them laundered every 2 weeks, then do my own ironing. It's sure worth that much and more to have them clean.
I have some of the cutest pictures Mae and I made. Cut out magazine pictures and pasted them on gown mats. Some are of Sat. evening pasts. Adds lots to my room.
I made some dandy corn fritters for supper last night and had some left for dinner today. It's so handy having some thing already fixed for quick brunch at work. The mail usually comes at noon and I have a time popping from stove to letters getting them read.
I'll sure take time to write Aunt Sarah later also to Pearl. Girls I've had several cards from Irvin Pounds with his address - gentle hint! Guess I'll write him too.
You've asked so many time about color of Martin's suit and I forget to answer. He wants brown mixture and its very popular too. A sort of red brown then he wants brown shoes before he comes home so of course I'll be able to get them then. He takes real good care of his appearance - as good as possible. He can spend a good deal time at Mae's or over to Sam's (he usually does) while I am at Topeka and sorts rough about for his meals down here. I feel safe enough about leaving him so much with Sam. They're pretty good roomies. And he likes Mrs. D.D. too she jollies with him so much. Don't mention anything about being afraid to leave him in your letters but you might tell him to make the best of everything while I'm away. I know where he is every minute for he gets out a certain time and I know he doesn't waste much getting here. he looks fine and never coughs one, since he had that cold.
Grace, it's about time you were writing again. I'd like to write lots more but will have to go to bed its 11:20 and I was up late last night. Guess I'll write on the other side tho. Say Mrs. Mussenbach  must want her fame as a poctiss to spread abroad. I saw two in the paper last week. Guess I'll send Carrie a card, and put my address on it. Hers is just Woodriver but I'll put c/o Washington School, Cleveland Ave.
I'm rather anxious to know the outcome of the settlement, so is Mae. Art asked Mae what she was going to do with her half. He's pretty busy making Xmas presents. Guess he don't want the worry of it right at the last. Must close. Write as often as you can. It's a deal to look forward to after school hours to expect mail. I think thats why Martin rushes home so.
Love to All,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least - Thanks for $15.00&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1912/10/23/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 1912 20:29:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Margaret Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1912/07/17/from-unknown-to-margaret-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18010776_0062.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-323" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18010776_0062.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140421_18010776_0062" width="1019" height="1547"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18020778_0065.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-322" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140421_18020778_0065.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140421_18020778_0065" width="1522" height="1040"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Unknown, To: Margaret Chandler
Mailed From: Dunlap, Iowa on July 17, 1912&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Margaret Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Margaret,
Did you see us wave when we left Pearl? We saw you kids out on the side walk. Were having a good time on the merry-go-round.
Your Sister,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Margaret Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1912/07/17/from-unknown-to-margaret-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 1912 00:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Grace Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/09/08/from-ruby-chandler-to-grace-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140505_16590652_0202.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-594" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140505_16590652_0202.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140505_16590652_0202" width="1507" height="1049"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140505_16591364_0203.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-595" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140505_16591364_0203.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140505_16591364_0203" width="1534" height="1042"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Grace Chandler
Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on September 8, 1911
Postcard Info: Embossed Comic Series No. 5475. Copyrighted 1911 by E.J. Haffner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Grace Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Grace:
Won't you even send me a card? Did you get those from Carmen? We received Bess' letter after I mailed Papa's. Glad to low she is doing so well. We went all over to the new high school today. It is just great. We're so glad Martin is to tie those studies. Write soon.
Lovingly,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Grace Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/09/08/from-ruby-chandler-to-grace-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 1911 22:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Bess Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/08/31/from-ruby-chandler-to-bess-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_17500591_0102.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-399" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_17500591_0102.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140425_17500591_0102" width="995" height="1491"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_17501440_0103.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-400" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_17501440_0103.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140425_17501440_0103" width="1536" height="1010"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Bess Chandler
Mailed From: Carmen, Oklahoma on August 31, 1911
Postcard Info: Summer Girls Series Number 155 Copyrighted 1910, By J. Marks NY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss  Bess Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Dear Sister:
Thought for sure we'd hear from you yesterday but didn't. Hope you're getting along fine. We read the children's cards. They were written just dandy. We're going to Oklahoma tomorrow and coming back on Saturday, I guess. School begins here the 11th. We all went to the beach of Arkansas river and went swimming while Ma looked on. Had a good teacher and think I can learn in a little while. Ase was out this evening for supper also. The other half, Mae and Ma have given us bathing scents. Will write when Mamma doesn't. She always writes so much there is nothing left for me to tell. Hoss' letter was just a line telling me to hurry and send plants and had several blank pages.
Love to all,
R.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Bess Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/08/31/from-ruby-chandler-to-bess-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 1911 23:48:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Bess Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/06/01/from-ruby-chandler-to-bess-chandler-2/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_18275300_0114.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-427" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_18275300_0114.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140425_18275300_0114" width="1528" height="1048"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_18280081_0115.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-428" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140425_18280081_0115.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140425_18280081_0115" width="1552" height="1045"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Bess Chandler
Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on June 1, 1911&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Bess Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Were so glad to get your letters yesterday. We will start home Sunday. Be sure to send me new chick book. Decided won't go to Oklahoma. I thought school began 14th or 16th. Are you ready to come out and stay? Wrote exam again today and the thing look mighty fine. Well, see you soon.
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Bess Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/06/01/from-ruby-chandler-to-bess-chandler-2/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 1911 00:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/05/20/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140430_17521016_0140.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-466" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140430_17521016_0140.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140430_17521016_0140" width="1529" height="995"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140430_17534224_0143.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-467" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/postcard-2014-20140430_17534224_0143.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140430_17534224_0143" width="1507" height="1021"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on May 20, 1911
Photo Info: Jimmy Ward Taking Mrs. Ward for her First Flight. Wichita. May 4. 11&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Papa,
This is a picture taken at the aviation meet here when we first came. A friend of Vinnie's took us in his auto to the ball game yesterday afternoon. Omaha vs. Wichita. A great game. We sent a package home yesterday. A book for Margaret and Lucerne. Tell Lucerne to read to Margaret.
Love to all,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1911/05/20/from-ruby-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 1911 23:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>