<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1930/12/31/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17205403_0241.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-663" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17205403_0241.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17205403_0241" width="2147" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17204221_0240.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-662" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17204221_0240.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17204221_0240" width="2147" height="3011"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17230938_0243.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-664" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17230938_0243.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17230938_0243" width="2147" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17225785_0242.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-665" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17225785_0242.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17225785_0242" width="2153" height="3011"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17243788_0245.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-666" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17243788_0245.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17243788_0245" width="2153" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17242642_0244.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-667" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140508_17242642_0244.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140508_17242642_0244" width="2153" height="3017"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1930/12/postcard-2014-20140528_18222793_0381.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-860" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1930/12/postcard-2014-20140528_18222793_0381.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140528_18222793_0381" width="2134" height="1178"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on December 31, 1930 Mailed Address: Mrs. E.H. Chandler Pearl, Illinois Return Address: Mrs. Sam Mullholland 421 E. Lewis Wichita, Kansas Wichita, Kansas December 31, 1930 Dearest Mama and Martin Received your letter yesterday also one from Bess saying John was led past with such a bad back. Said he suffered terribly the past two night. I want to write her again today. I've written Grace so maybe I'll get such debts settled before the new year. I was reminded of my position Saturday on account of dill times. He told me I had done marvelously well, etc and if I needed references to tell them to come to him. I was there just a month. I'm not going to look for anything else for we'll be moving soon. The van will go to Fredonia for out things Saturday and Sunday and we'll be in by the 8th. I hope mostly straightened up by that time. It's petty far out on N. Laurence 3701. Gene will be transferred to Central International Mediate for the new semester. That school is real close to the golf course. Sam will bring him back and forth. Sam goes to work on an oil lease for the present out 3 miles starting the 2nd. So, he is lucky to get anything as many as are having let out. Grove not Bob have anything in sight either. Those of our fame;y who have good positions are in luck sure enough. Bess Doesn't write so optimistic either but she doesn't mind any hardships where her family is connected. She surely is big hearted. Her biggest worry is John's sickness and I surely hope he improves soon. Took sick the next day after Christmas she said. Mama you didn't say if you got my box of candy. We mailed it the same time as the letter you received. I hope it wasn't lost. I was surprised about Lucille having another girl. I wonder how Aunt Belle is now? We had cards from Virginia and Dr. I didn't send one to Va. as I didn't get her address and I was too busy to get it. Mother Davis is growing weaker. A.V. [Arthur Vincent] provides a nurse and they have a girl, too. So that is all he can do. He just can't get there often on account of his work. Mother Muir is fine - makes quilts all the time but it costs them plenty to get them quilted. At least $8 a piece and they drive to Sedgewick to take them to a woman who does it for them Gene is raising the roof with his bugle. He likes to practice on it. His vacation lasts until the 4th. Ours up here is the 8th so that gives us 4 days to get our furniture straightened. I'll have to cook with electricity as we'll be out beyond the gas main and water line. But the owner says the improvements will be extended right away. The house is brick and seems to be nice enough. Will tell you more about it after we get in. This house belongs to another concern Sam is interested in and the partner seems  very anxious for us to get in and look after things. The advantage in going there is the rental is free and that means a lot at preset. You surely have had some game, haven't you? I'd like to eat rabbit with you. Gene's out in the sun - bareheaded just tearing around on his roller skates. It is so pretty out. We had the one snow and the river was full of ice blocks at that time but it has been so mild for a week. I surely hope it will remain mild for the most of the winter and for your sake I hope you don't have such cold weather if you have to be in Pearl. That house is too hard for you to manage through the winter and I wish I could help you, but it will be rather difficult for me too so I'll be glad when spring comes. I surely hope Martin is better by now. Tell him he's better drop us a line. There isn't very much to write since I last wrote. Wish I had a birthday presently for you - but wishes are not very substantial. Anyway I hope you keep real will till your next birthday and hope to see you before your next. Love to both of you, Ruby, Sam, and Gene</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland</category><category>Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1930/12/31/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1930 23:13:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1930/12/26/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-3/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16502141_0325.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-803" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16502141_0325.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16502141_0325" width="1631" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16501161_0324.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-804" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16501161_0324.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16501161_0324" width="1637" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16510406_0327.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-805" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16510406_0327.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16510406_0327" width="1619" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16505426_0326.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-806" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16505426_0326.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16505426_0326" width="1631" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16512644_0329.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-807" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16512644_0329.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16512644_0329" width="1625" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16511663_0328.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-808" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16511663_0328.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16511663_0328" width="1631" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16515102_0331.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-809" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16515102_0331.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16515102_0331" width="1625" height="2561"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16514122_0330.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-810" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16514122_0330.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140526_16514122_0330" width="1625" height="2555"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1930/12/postcard-2014-20140528_16532561_0337.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-820" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1930/12/postcard-2014-20140528_16532561_0337.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140528_16532561_0337" width="2141" height="1145"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140526_16514122_0330.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
&lt;span style="line-height: 1.5;"&gt;Mailed From: Wichita, Kansas on December 26, 1930&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mailing Address:
Mrs. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Return Address:
Mrs. Sam Mullholland
427 E. Lewis
Wichita, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wrapper on your box came from Mae. She sent me a coral necklace and hose to Sam and Gene.
Wichita, Kansas
December 25, '30
Dearest Mama and Mart
Since I have an hour or so left over I thought I'd get your letter answered today and let you know how we spent Christmas.
We went down to Grove's and Inez's along about 10 am but had our own tree and gifts at home early this a.m. Inez had a small tree but we all exchanged candy except that they gave Gene gloves and hose. He also got 2 lovely pair of golf hose from Mae and Art and Bob gave him a dollar. He faired awfully well considering things. Sam gave me hose and I gave him a tie. We gave Gene a bugle, books and a drinking set. A girl here in town brought down a big box of chocolates with a note, "Mostly for Gene" on it. She came over to my house at El Dorado on Thanksgiving and ever since, she has been so generous. Kathryn Hutchinson is her name. I didn't even send them a card. I didn't miss very many though. I had a stack of them. An awfully nice one from Dr. Garrison. I noticed Mart had forwarded it from Pearl. Was glad to get a line from all the family so soon again. So I'll write them all and then I'll be all set to hear again.
Don't be surprised when I tell you to change our address soon. We aim to get our furniture over in about two weeks and move into a house in the 3700 block on North Lawrence. But I'll let you know when we do. Just write here and I'll drop a line later. I don't know yet how long I'll be at Dr.'s as there is such a slump in business. He told me to come back though and I noticed he paid off several others as he wouldn't be needing them but of course even he doesn't know how business will continue. Sam will go to work for an oil Co. here Jan 1. Don't know his duties exactly - but its with oil rigs, etc. Which is something in our favor.
We had a lovely dinner at Inez's. Grove had bought a turkey and Bob had one given to him through the Sheriff so he and his girl and a boy friend also a friend of Grove's besides us were there. Mae and Art didn't come because they thought Dick was to be at home and and he was sent to Ottawa, Kansas on a job this a.m. so Mae's plans were all broken into. They're rather at sea anyway on account of Mother Davis being so low. She can't get well now so its just a matter of how long her constitution can hold out. She surely is hearty - in frame that is - but has sinking spells and is bedfast. Inez has a colored girl so we didn't have to do much all day. We had turkey with dressing, asparagus - buttered, mashed potatoes, giblet gravy with hard boiled egg diced in it, cranberry jelly, pumpkin pie, cake, coffee and rolls. We had fruit cocktail made of grapefruit, orange, pears, peaches, and some cherry in it. We also had waldorfaud salad. This cook had put a little sweet pickle in the waldorfaud and it was awfully good for a change. We had celery too. So we had such a big dinner and no work and they wouldn't let me bring a thing. So it sure was easy on me. You know about how much time one has left when working. I made some candy last night and this a.m. and I'm going to mail a box to you and I was sorry not to get it to you before. I only sent Annie a story book but I think I can get a box of candy to her for New Year's Day. I just write her address c/o of State Hospital, Dixon Illinois. I never have had a line from them either so a person never can tell whether she gets anything or not. I was so glad to hear of Lucerne's baby doing better. I thought I might get a letter written to her too but owe one to Grace first, so I'll try and get it written tonight.
We have had such nice rather the past week but it looks different tonight, like it might snow. But I guess we might expect winter from now on.
Gene will be out of school for about then days so he'll get in a lot of play. He has two or three friends he visits back and forth with and I know their people are nice so I don't worry about him just so I know where he'll be all the time. He is awfully good about sticking around home and he reads a lot and does quite a bit around the house. He comes down to the store, runs errands and goes to a show now and then, so his time is pretty well filled up.
Mr. Skaggs has had a serious attack of something like diabetes. He's a man a great deal like Uncle Jim was and I wouldn't be surprised if he didn't go like he did. Mrs. Skaggs wrote me they will stay in Kansas City until he goes to hospital for a general exam. So I'll have to write her soon again. You know we pay her storage for our furniture but I want it over here so bad and now think we can get a good house reasonable. Must quit now. Write soon. Hope all well.
Lots Love,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1930/12/26/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-3/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 1930 22:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1927/11/21/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-2/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17143021_0283.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-745" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17143021_0283.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140519_17143021_0283" width="2051" height="3125"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17141797_0282.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-746" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17141797_0282.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140519_17141797_0282" width="2045" height="3125"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17145349_0285.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-747" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17145349_0285.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140519_17145349_0285" width="2045" height="3131"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17144003_0284.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-748" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/postcard-2014-20140519_17144003_0284.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140519_17144003_0284" width="2039" height="3119"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1927/11/postcard-2014-20140528_17554163_0365.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-842" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1927/11/postcard-2014-20140528_17554163_0365.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140528_17554163_0365" width="2147" height="1157"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1927/11/postcard-2014-20140528_17553256_0364.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-841" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1927/11/postcard-2014-20140528_17553256_0364.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20140528_17553256_0364" width="2141" height="1145"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland, To: Jeanette Knox Chandler
Mailed From: Fredonia, Kansas on November 21, 1927&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mailing Address:
Mrs. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Return Address:
Mrs. Sam Mullholland
Fredonia, Kansas
937 Jackson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fredonia. Monday.
Dearest Mama, Mart, and Lu
I guess that includes all that are left at home now. Quite a bunch of us got away all at once.
There was another wreck on the C&amp;amp;A so we were detoured into Kansas City via Mo. Pac. you know we only had an hour between trains, so of course we missed our Santa Fe.
Sam went to the office at Union Station to get our tickets routed over another R.R. as there was no other Santa Fe so we finally got transferred to the Mo. Pac. to Fredonia. Changing trains once we got here at 10:50 Saturday night. It was easy to spend the time in K.C. We checked our stuff went up town for breakfast, window shopped, and after dinner we went to the new lovers midland theatre and got out in time to get our train at 4:30.
It had been snowing out this way. Wonder if you had anywhere. It was so pleasant in K.C. we were sure surprised to step out into snow where we changed trains.
The first person we ran into at Kansas City was Beverly Davis and his girl was with him. He was just out of the hospital and getting a train to Wichita. Had been in K.C a month. Had his knee operated and thinks he won't have to use a crutch. He looked terrible but after expert care maybe he'll improve. He said Marvel and D.D. had been there a little while.
I had a letter from Inez saying she'd be over for a few days. She thought I'd be home last week so I don't know whether Thanksgiving will interfere with her coming or not.
Mrs. Skagg, the landlady, is just able to be up. Her trouble seems to be gall stones. The Dr. told her to be operated, but she says she doesn't intend to.
The club is to meet with me tomorrow. It is on the program that way or I'd not have it for I didn't even intend going but the president said she'd have to phone everyone and I'd have to get someone to exchange with me, so I told her to go ahead and let them come. All I have to do is to have my house clean.
Several neighbors came in yesterday to express sympathy. One of them brought me in a hot mince pie for dinner. I sure was needing it too as I didn't get anything and we didn't want to go out for dinner.
Some of you write soon. I hope Mama feel pretty week. I don't feel I am any help to you Mama so far away but wish I could help you decide what to do. But you probably can do that better far yourself -and after a little time goes by.
This is all for now. You write to Martin.
Lots of Love,
Ruby&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Ruby Chandler Mullholland</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Jeanette Knox Chandler</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1927/11/21/from-ruby-chandler-mullholland-to-jeanette-knox-chandler-2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 1927 23:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>