<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about Mentions Military Service)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/mentions-military-service.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-9/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2094" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15153571_0021.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15153571_0021" width="3264" height="1950"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2095" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15154562_0022.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15154562_0022" width="3307" height="1937"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2096" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15155345_0023.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15155345_0023" width="3280" height="1937"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2097" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15160310_0024.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15160310_0024" width="3301" height="1960"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on January 30, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany
30 Jan 1919
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Received letter from Papa today dated Jan 10th. Doesn't take mail very long to get here now. Certainly was glad to get it. Glad to know Ruby has recovered from the flu. First I had heard of her sickness. Sure is good to know you are all well. I'm still on the same job but expect to attend school at Coblens commencing next Monday. Cobblers is a pretty large city. Not much news about when we will leave but general impression is that we will start about the 1st of March. Certainly hope we do cause I'm mighty anxious to get home. Picked up some Radio press last night. Said 42nd and 32nd divisions would be first complete national guard units home and 77th Division would be first drafted division home. Like to get home and bid in some of there jobs that are on bulletin.
Having a show here nearly every night. Will mail you some of the programs if I can find them. Having a German grand opera tonight but I'm on duty and can't go. However they're having another one tomorrow night so guess I'll go to it. Doesn't cost anything. Have a swell theatre, looks just like the ones in the states.
Forgot to mention that I received letter from Papa other day enclosing copy of Mr. Doocy's letter. Glad you mailed them a copy of my letter. If I'm ever in Pittsfield I'll call on them.
Found out about my allotment today. it's still infect and will continue until I get out of the army.
Hope you're getting it regularly. I've been feeling just fine. Feel like I want to get out and run all the time. Have a great big feather bed to sleep in. Get lots of sleep, plenty to eat and not much work. I'll be all ready to go to work after I see you all and visit Ruby and Grace.
Think we get one months extra pay when we're discharged. That will by me a suit of clothes. It wont take me long to make enough to fit myself out with plenty of clothing. Certainly would like to get into a suit of civilian clothes again.
Rumor has it that when we leave here we sail on the Rhine up to Belgium. Sounds plausible.
Division is ranting 14 day leaves now to men who wish to visit relatives in Scotland, Ireland, England, or Italy. Guess that doesn't include me case if I have any relatives in any of those countries I don't know it. Besides I haven't the funds to provide for such a trip. Wouldn't mind going to Italy. They say Rome is a wonderful place. I'll be satisfied if they'll just send me home though. Don't think I'll ever cross the Atlantic again, once I get on the other side. Hows Knox making it? Certainly was tickled to hear about Audrey talking in her sleep and saying "God Bless her little heart." Ha ha.
I certainly did get the Christmas box and I want to say that I enjoyed it ever so much. I've a lot of back mail coming yet if it ever gets here.
Be glad when the Conference gets a peace treaty ready for Germany to sing. Hope they get things settled in Russia. See where our troops are fighting there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-9/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 1919 22:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/11/02/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-27/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2013" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09075509_0048.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09075509_0048" width="1423" height="2197"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2014" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09083048_0050.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09083048_0050" width="1448" height="2211"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2015" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09085290_0052.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09085290_0052" width="1441" height="2205"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: France on November 2, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France Nov. 2nd '18
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
Thought  I'd write a few lines this pm while I had the stationary handy. Am still in hospital so have had no mail since last writing. Wont get any until I get back to my organization. I'm feeling fine and dandy and am up all the time during the day. Will be getting out before long. Notice in paper where Turkey has capitulated and it looks as though Austria will follow suit so that will leave Germany all alone. Looks as though the war was approaching the grand finale. I'd certainly love to see it over by Christmas. You've all read of the Lt. Mitice drive. Our division started that drive and went all the way through it besides holding the line for quite a while after it was over. Can't mention anything about our work since that time. Noticed that in the paper so concluded 'twas permissible for me to mention it. The allies have been doing some tall scrapping, especially the Americans. They had the hardest piece of ground to take of any of them and they're still scrapping.
Well its about supper time so must stop and peddle the coffee. I'm on K.P. here. ha. Hope you are all we'll. Don't worry any about me.
Lovingly,
Martin
Crp M. W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 FBSC - AEF&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/11/02/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-27/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 1918 16:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/10/24/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-28/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2021" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09344020_0058.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09344020_0058" width="1735" height="2621"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2022" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09343131_0057.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09343131_0057" width="1707" height="2604"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2023" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09345864_0060.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09345864_0060" width="1766" height="2626"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2024" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09344889_0059.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09344889_0059" width="1740" height="2607"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2025" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09351506_0062.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09351506_0062" width="1757" height="2621"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: France on October 24, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France Oct. 24th - 1918
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Haven't written for so long that I guess you all will think I've quit writing altogether. This is first chance I've had to write for some time. Wrote you the 3rd of Oct. but had no chance to mail it. I've received lots letters from all of you since last writing. Have received two from Grace enclosing Kodaks of Audrey. They sure were dandy pictures especially the last one (the one taken when she was lying on the bed) I've been in hospital since the 18th. Am getting along OK and expect to be out soon. Got sick while at the front. Am enclosing a christmas pkg. coupon but don't suppose it will reach you in time. If it doesn't, don't worry any about sending an xmas pkg.
have certainly had a nice time during past two months. Tell you all about it when we get home. Been quite a bit of peace talk floating around lately but I'm not very sanguine. How are the girls getting along in Wichita? Guess I'd better ask them though. Sure glad Margaret and Lucerne are attending school there instead of at home. See in the paper where the Liberty Loan went over the top by 150 million. That's about what we all expected. People over there sure are keeping their end up.
Guess I wont get any more mail until I get back to the outfit. Don't know when that will be. I'm feeling pretty good now except that I'm rather weak. Heard Ruby was expecting next month. Sure hope she comes through ok.
We've een having some very rainy weather over here for past month. Nothing unusual though. How's Knox getting along with school? Who is his teacher?
This ought to get home just about Papa's birthday so dad, here's wishing you many happy returns of the day.
Am going to Answer Grace and Lorin's letter soon as I get some stationary. In fact I'll answer everybody's letters and I'll try and write you all real often while I have the chance.
The Allies have certainly been delivering some fearful wallops to the Huns. Kinda got 'em hollering for peace now.
Well must close. Hope this finds you all well. Don't worry any about me.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/10/24/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-28/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 1918 16:35:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/10/12/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-7/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2028" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_13122680_0063.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_13122680_0063" width="2938" height="2469"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2029" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_13123666_0064.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_13123666_0064" width="3027" height="2469"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martim Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed On: October 12, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oct. 12 1918
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
Didn't geta chance to mail my letter of 3rd so will add few more lines. Received letter from papa other day and sure glad to get it. Papa keeps them coming pretty regularly. Haven't much time to write but don't know much to write anyway. Certainly been busy past month and lots to put up with. No one kicking through, nights are very cold now and have been having lots of rainy weather. Have travelled considerably since last writing. Mostly on foot.
Sure would like to see the Germans surrender so we could come home. The allies are giving them the dickens on all sides. Heard about German's request for an armistice. Don't think they will get any satisfaction until they pull their troops in.
I've been feeling fine and dandy. Hope you all are well.
I'll answer Grace's letter at first opportunity. Don't know the girl's address in Wichita. Bess didn't mention it in her letter. I'll have to close now. Going to try and rustle something to eat. Everybody write.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/10/12/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-7/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 1918 20:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/09/29/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-40/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2144" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11220876_0076.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11220876_0076" width="1608" height="2373"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2145" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11221906_0078.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11221906_0078" width="1605" height="2369"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2146" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11225868_0080.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11225868_0080" width="1578" height="2366"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2147" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11230891_0082.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11230891_0082" width="1549" height="2364"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2149" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11231330_0084.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11231330_0084" width="1627" height="2370"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2150" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11232368_00861.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11232368_0086" width="1617" height="2365"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2151" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11244102_0088.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11244102_0088" width="1635" height="2368"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2152" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11245148_0090.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11245148_0090" width="1626" height="2365"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2153" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11250181_0092.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11250181_0092" width="1610" height="2374"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2155" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11251382_00941.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11251382_0094" width="1627" height="2375"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2156" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11252479_0096.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11252479_0096" width="1621" height="2380"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2157" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11260993_0098.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11260993_0098" width="1624" height="2380"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2158" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11262027_0100.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11262027_0100" width="1596" height="2378"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2159" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11263068_0102.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11263068_0102" width="1620" height="2377"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2160" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_11264113_0104.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_11264113_0104" width="1621" height="2381"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Little Silver, New Jersey on September 29th, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill
Pike County&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sept 29th
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Received papa's letter day before yesterday and another today and also received mama's and Bess' dandy letters enclosing Johns and Aunt Anna's and I certainly enjoyed them all. Was mighty glad to get them. Was first mail I've received since leaving Ft. Bliss. Am over at club tonight. Was at YMCA Thursday and Friday nights. Had a social Thursday night. In fact they have on every Thursday. Good program. Served ice cream and cake. Friday night was formal opening and dedication of YMCA. Had good speaking and good program.  Enjoyed it very much. These sure are good places to pass away time at night. All kinds of amusements. Lots of good books, both at YMCA and Club. The people here are very hospitable and some notable financial powers live in immediate vicinity of this place. Wilsons son-in-law lives only four miles from here. Was glad to get Lesley Wildt's address. Have been wanting it for past year. He and I used to chum together quite a bit. Haven't located Lake Denmark yet but will do so tomorrow and if not very far will get to see him. It is now rumored that we sail about the 3rd of next month. But have heard nothing definite but think we will leave pretty soon. Just found out yesterday that I can have all or part of my pay sent home by government so I'll put in a $20.00 allotment to be sent home each month. Had to give name of some relative today who should be notified in case of my death or an accident. All preparations indicate we will leave shortly. They're not fixing up camp very much and wont build anything or order any stoves for us, and it's pretty cold here too, so i guess we will leave shortly. I have another horse now. It's a fine big black horse. Awful powerful and can run like the wind. It's a great pet too. Did you get the Battalion picture ok? You didn't mention it but suppose you did. I'll try and have my picture taken with horse before I leave and send to you. Awful glad the children are getting along OK in school and mighty glad Lucerne can play so well. Wish I could have been there when Sam and all the rest were at home. I'd like mighty welt see Audrey Grace. To think I've a close relative that I can't see and don't when when I can - I'll bet she is a cute kid. We had General Inspecting this morning. Had all out filled equipment laid out and cleaned up nicely. Also had pistol inspection. We all have 45 Caliber Colts automatics. Sure are good guns. Thats all the weapons we have. Don't stand much show if we should happen to be compelled to repair or construct line of communication under fire. Of course we wont fight any this winter. Will probably train all winter in France and be ready for spring. Lots of men leaving everyday now for France. Uncle Sam is gathering them over there pretty fast.
Golly I'll certainly appreciate the sweater the girls are knitting. It will come in mighty handy. Yes, mama I've heard the songs you mentioned. "Over There" and "America Here's my Boy." Thats about all they sing out here. They all like "Over There" best of all. Glad to hear Aunt Sarah received her back pension money. Sure hope she stays well and is feeling good. Golly papa I'd like o be there and help out with the work. I know what apple season is there. All the crops through Missouri and Kansas are best ever so the farmers said when we passed through there. Is Grimaly working at "Dr." Papa? Sure hope you learn to use that bug OK  cause its a great labor saver and you can do so much better with it after learning to use it. What branch of service is Wade Maynard in? Guess there will be quite a few go over before the war is over. Saw in paper yesterday where the Pope's peace proposal had failed and he predicts the war will last for 3 years yet. Gee everything is high out here. Bacon is 47 cents pound. Eggs 70 cents dozen. Our laundry in Fr. Bliss cost each man $1.75 per month. No matter how much or how little we sen but I sent min in to Long Branch other day and it cost me $1.59 so it will amount to quite a little in a month. Well must close . Everybody write often. If can do so will give you address soon as we get across.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/09/29/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-40/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 1918 18:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/05/13/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-34/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2090" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_14410079_0008.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_14410079_0008" width="1950" height="2412"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2091" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_14411679_0010.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_14411679_0010" width="1951" height="2417"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: France on May 13, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France May 13th 1918
Dearest Papa, Mama, &amp;amp; all,
Wrote you several days ago but it came back yesterday account containing too much news. Ha. Also one sent back which I had to Ruby so now I'll have to do them over. I received 2 letters from Papa yesterday. One dated in Feb forwarded from other company and one dated in April. That makes 7 letters I've received from you all in lat 3 days. Sure was mighty glad to get them. Ruby, Grace, Lorin, and Bess all wrote dandy long letters. Very much surprised to hear of Grover's marriage. Hope they get along OK. Bess told me of Lee Maynard's marriage also. Lots of the fellows under 31 getting married since last June. Ha.
Guess I can't tell you much news. My last effort was a failure have quite a bit of time tonight so guess I'll write everybody a letter. Ruby, Grace, and Bess. Has Bess gone to Wichita yet? Ruby said she was coming. Well I finally received my service record and will get my 6 months pay this pay day. It will be $20.00 shy account of an allotment that you all didn't get and therefore due me. You remember I told you last Jan that when I changed the allotment last November it cancelled the former one and the 20.00 for Nov. wasn't sent home and on the Jan pay roll it was marked due me but wasn't on the pay role this month.  Guess I'll get it next month. I can use the frances very nicely. Am out of Soviet articles. Are you getting the allotment regularly? Glad you got the insurance policy. I never have received any of the packages you mentioned having sent. Don't have the last idea where they are. Hope papa gets that raise to 12. That wont be so bad.
Were having dandy weather except for rain. Everybody has their garden in. We still draw rations and do our own cooking. Like it fine. Guess you all feel the effects of the war. Relative foodstuffs, etc. I see by the "Communique" from Paris that the 3rd Liberty loan was a grand success.
The YMCAs are going great work over here. Furnish all sorts of entertainment. There were two American girls sang at YMCA here last week. Sure was a sight for sore eyes. I notice they kept gazing at a shell hole in the roof and were rather startled every time on of our "berthas" sent over a kiss to the Kaiser. Ha.
Well I must close and get busy on the rest of the letters. Don't pass this one around cause I'm going to write them all one just like it. Ha.
Am feeling great and getting along OK. Don't worry about me. Will write again, soon.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/05/13/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-34/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 1918 21:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/04/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-14/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2237" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150102_14060856_0199.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150102_14060856_0199" width="2492" height="1853"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2238" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150102_14061661_0200.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150102_14061661_0200" width="2483" height="1867"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: France on April 30th, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pvt. M. W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 F.B.S.C
42nd Division=A.E.F.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France April 30th, 1918
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Received Mama's dandy long letter yesterday dated April 1st and mighty glad to get it. Wish you would keep them coming. I haven't received my serve record yet consequently no pay and don't have the slightest idea when I will.
Certainly is disgusting to hear about the Pro Germans around there. They should be put in jail as German sympathizers. I wish some Govt. official would hear Heddler make a remark like "Dog collars should be put on all soldiers and called Wilson's pups." That's German sympathy pure and simple. I wish some of them could come in contact with these Germans. I consider it great sport to elevate a big fat german on the end of a Bayonet and hear him squeal. They're just like their government - greedy and inhuman. I'll surely be glad when they are cleaned up which, of course, will be the eventual outcome of this war.
Nothing new to write. Getting along OK and feeling fine. If you can secure copy of Kansas City post of Mar. 14th you will see some interesting news. Grinsley might get you a copy. Hope Bill gets in good branch of service if he is selected. Wish I could have been there when the sausage arrived. Ha.
Hope you have good luck with your garden down by Quarry.
We've been having lots rain over here. Wish it would dry up. Well I must stop, all of you write and don't worry about me. I'll write as often as I can.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/04/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-14/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 1918 21:07:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/03/19/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-23/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1979" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_13305031_0012.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_13305031_0012" width="2439" height="3689"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1980" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_13311342_0014.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_13311342_0014" width="2441" height="3685"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1981" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_13313558_0016.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_13313558_0016" width="2422" height="3695"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1982" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_13332663_0018.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_13332663_0018" width="1254" height="1117"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Ahrwieler, Germany on March 19th, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
Received latter from Papa yesterday and was mighty glad to get it. Pretty near every mail brings in a letter from Papa. Well, theres new dope out now that we wont leave for some time. They got orders not to turn over equipment until further notice. Darn it! Seems like something comes up every time to change things. Will enclose the speech delivered us by Gen. Pershing up on Rhine last Sunday. Sure was a dandy review. Everything went lovely.
Been having some rain and snow lately but today is pretty day.
Heard rumor that we will go through France and not up the Rhine. Certainly hope it isn't true. Sure would hate to go through France. probably have to lay in France for couple of weeks if we go through there.
We don't belong to the 4th Army Corps any more. Are now 3rd Army reserve. Certainly hope we start for home soon cause I'm mighty anxious to get there. I'll be sure and fill out the blank you received from Pittsfield. Are they just for men from Pike County?
Well, haven't much time to write this and don't know much more to write. So will close. Hope you are all well
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/03/19/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-23/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 1918 20:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/01/13/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-33/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2086" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_14253691_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_14253691_0002" width="2479" height="3243"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2087" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_14262087_0004.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_14262087_0004" width="2472" height="3234"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on January 13, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany
Jan 13th, 1918
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
No mail since last writing. Expecting to receive my back mail most any day. Sure be glad when it comes. Nothing new to write about. Still having mild weather.
Am working in Message Center here. Recording correspondence, telegrams, etc.  Doesn't require much clerical ability. Work from 8 am to 5 pm and in addition, work half night every fourth night. Don't have much to do at night but keep pretty busy during the day. have a good warm place to sleep. Getting good meals here. Have been feeling extremely good past month.
Notice in paper when they are busting men out of service, at a rapid rate in the states. Will certainly be glad when we get back. Don't have the least idea when that will be. Hear lots of rumors but, of course, one can't believe them. The A.E.F. has got an Old Maids sewing circle backed clear of the map when it comes to starting rumors.
Was much surprised to hear of Colonel Roosevelt's death. The Country will sure miss him.
Our signal Corps Radio picks up the states, Russia, Honolulu and many other places. Get lots of press from the states.
The German people treat us very good. Do almost anything for a fellow. Guess they're depending a great deal on the U.S. helping them out in the future.
Well must close for this time. Hope you are all well. Will write again soon.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Enclosed</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/01/13/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-33/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 1918 21:24:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1917/12/17/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-11/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2173" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12573757_0118.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12573757_0118" width="1475" height="2254"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2174" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12580219_0120.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12580219_0120" width="1478" height="2245"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2175" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12581252_0122.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12581252_0122" width="1481" height="2238"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2176" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12582790_0124.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12582790_0124" width="1469" height="2248"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2177" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12584466_0126.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12584466_0126" width="1475" height="2242"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2178" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12590134_0128.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12590134_0128" width="1465" height="2238"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2179" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12591167_0130.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12591167_0130" width="1474" height="2245"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2180" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_12592245_0132.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_12592245_0132" width="1466" height="2257"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2181" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13000774_0134.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13000774_0134" width="1469" height="1027"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: New Jersey on December 17, 1917&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill
Pike County&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dec 16th, '17
Dearest Folks,
Have received 2 letters from Papa since last writing. Guess you'll think I've quit writing altogether. I've written twice. But as usual didn't mail them. They weren't very long letters anyway. Just a note.
Have been working like the dickens past week. It has snowed every day. Now 8:30 pm and we just got through loading our combat wagons, trucks, motorcycles, and other boxes and will load the horses tomorrow and leave Tuesday for sure so you needn't write me anymore until you hear from me again. Needn't mention to anyone that we have gone.
Will write you as often as possible from over there but don't expect any descriptions of country, etc cause it isn't allowed.
Got letter from Chas Morgan at St. Louis other day. It was in the dead letter office for some time account he didn't put my organization on envelope. Will enclose it. Today is Knox's birthday. Wish I had something to send. I'm broke cause didn't draw any pay this month.
I haven't read the insurance policy yet. Guess they will mail it direct to you. I changed my mind and made it for $10,000.00 in case I did you will get about $58.00 per month for 20 years and in case of death of beneficiary it goes to next closest relative and sundown until it is all paid. Again if I should be disabled I would receive a pretty nice income. It goes $6.50 per month on $10,000.00. That will leave me about 3.00 per month which I think will be all I'll need. Did you ever hear in regard to increase on my allotment? Sure hope you get it.
I'm feeling fine and have plenty of warm clothing and will make it OK so don't worry about me. We have a dandy Captain. He is always looking out for our health and comfort.
Well I'll stop and turn in cause I'm sure tired.
Here's wishing everybody a merry merry Christmas and Happy New Years and hope I'll be with you on the next Xmas.
Knox here's best wishes for a happy birthday and hope I'll see a big strapping fellow when I get back.
Will let you hear from me soon as can.
Lots love to all,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Letter Enclosed:
&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2184" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1917/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13241294_0136.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13241294_0136" width="1482" height="2234"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2185" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1917/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13242811_0138.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13242811_0138" width="1464" height="2230"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2186" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1917/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13243827_0140.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13243827_0140" width="1461" height="2235"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2187" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1917/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13245819_0142.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13245819_0142" width="1480" height="2237"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2188" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1917/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13251110_0144.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13251110_0144" width="1475" height="2228"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2189" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1917/12/postcard-2014-20141231_13252151_0146.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141231_13252151_0146" width="1461" height="2228"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;St. Louis, MO.
Antlers Hotel
18 &amp;amp; Olive Sts.
November 25, 1917&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Martin Chandler
Camp Vail, N.J.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Martin,
I have been reading your letters to the Tribune and have been much impressed by them and could constrain myself no longer from writing you a few lines of commendation. I am much gratified to know that some of the Pearl boys are "doing their bit," and a little more. I have, however, not much to say for myself, as I am not in active military service, but, believe me I do my share of moral support, such as proclaiming my american spirit, buying liberty bonds, etc. I did however, apply for Army Officers Reserve, but was unfortunate in that, a german letter carrier failed to deliver my first appointment in time (he is now out of service, you may be assured), the second comp you know, demanded a higher standard of men. Consequently, I did not make it. I was too young and had no military service.
As I am already in one branch of government service and have been attending a university here the past to years, I have hesitated to join as a private, I shall when I am really needed.
Well, Martin, I have used much ink in weakly justifying myself for not being in active service, but I am firmly convinced that every able bodied young man who is not in military, should have reasons as good or even better than I have.
There are many Germans in St. Louis, which affords many opportunities for one to express his patriotism.
I heard that your sisters were down here some time back, but I did not get to see them. I rarely see any one from Pearl. My brother Ray is staying with me now.
I hope you have an excellent Thanksgiving. I am sure I shall have.
We, university students have a big turkey supper on Wednesday, then a big "pep" parade! Shirt-tails out, etc. Big football game between our school and St. Louis University Thursday. I shall be there. I still feel like a high-school boy of 18, even thought I am over 25 but that is not old for University. Martin there is nothing better than school days, that is one reason I am having so many of them.
I suppose you know Martin Schlepper and his sister. They are here. Martin is out with us (at the Washington U.) and his sister is going to Brown's Business College. Fine boy is Martin.
Well Martin if you find a moment to spare when writing to your friend, let me have a line or so.
Wishing you rapid promotion, and the very best of luck, I  am ever,
Your Friend
Morgan, Chas E.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1917/12/17/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-11/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 1917 20:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>