<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about Sent While Martin was in the Military)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/sent-while-martin-was-in-the-military.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/06/25/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-20/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1960" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_11554711_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_11554711_0002" width="2299" height="1517"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1961" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_11561349_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_11561349_0002" width="2296" height="1521"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1962" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_11563069_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_11563069_0002" width="2298" height="1522"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1963" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_11564622_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_11564622_0002" width="2299" height="1516"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Soldier's Postal Service on June 25, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PVT. M.W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 F.B.S.C.
A.E.F.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;June 15th
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
No mail since last writing. Don't know of anything new to write so will cut this short. Raining today pretty hard. Of course hard very often. It generally pours. Am feeling good and getting along OK. Wrote grace few mins ago. Forgot to mention that I received dandy long letter from her few days ago. Has Bess gone to Wichita yet? Will Ruby come home when Sam goes? Was in hope he wouldn't come. Guess the boys at Taylor will be leaving pretty soon if they haven't already.
How does that new ditch work? You know I've never seen that. Guess there will be quite a few new things for me to do around there if I come back. Think we will be paid tomorrow. Wont take me long to get rid of mine. A need a supply of tobacco and a razor if I can find one. Think they have some Gillette safety razors here for $5.00 and I'm going to get one if can find any. I draw $10.10 per month including foreign services pay and insurance and all amounts to $26.50 so thats a total of $36.60 per month. That's not so bad. Of course we get paid in French money. 1 Franc equals about 17.5 c or about 5 Fr. 70 cents to the dollar.
The Americans sure spend lots of money over here. The francs don't seem to be valued as much as an American piece of money. They think nothing of spending 100 Fr while if it was a $20.00 bill they would go slower with it. Eggs cost 5 fr a dozen and all the groceries etc are about 2 or 3 times as much as in the states. A can of tomatoes that costs 15 cents over there costs about 60 cents here. We get out washing done up good, though, very cheap.
Well must stop. Will write again soon as get a chance. Everybody write often.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Sent While Martin was in the Military</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/06/25/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-20/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 1918 18:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>