<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about To: Amelia J. Wiggins)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/to-amelia-j-wiggins.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Betty, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1942/02/24/from-betty-to-amelia-j-wiggins-2/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2830" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150323_11581752_0677.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150323_11581752_0677" width="1497" height="958"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2831" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150323_11582721_0678.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150323_11582721_0678" width="953" height="1533"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Betty Ann Tilley, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Topeka, Kansas on February 24, 1942&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. B. A. Tilley
1312 Harrison
Topeka, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins
725 Waverly Route 5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tokepa, Kansas
Feb. 24-42
Dearest Auntie,
It isn't because we forgot you dear that we do not write but I am so busy all the time. This house is so big and always extra work to be done. Bertie comes usually of noon lunch and I try to write Harold every day. He is in Watertown, South Dakota. Mother not very well. She occasionally dries dishes for me but that is about all she can do. Hire very little help. Bert, Louie, and Harold are all pretty well. I keep fair. Hope darling you and your little pet are both all right. Wish you would write us a card.
Love,
Niece Betty
1312 Harrison&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Betty Ann Tilley</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1942/02/24/from-betty-to-amelia-j-wiggins-2/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 1942 17:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Betty Tilley, To: Amelua J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1941/06/30/from-betty-tilley-to-amelua-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2808" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_10362360_0662.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_10362360_0662" width="2443" height="3022"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2810" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1941/06/postcard-2014-20150321_10364247_0666.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_10364247_0666" width="1787" height="1081"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2811" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/1941/06/postcard-2014-20150321_10363536_0665.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_10363536_0665" width="1737" height="1069"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Betty Tilley, To:  Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Topeka, Kansas on June 30, 1941&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins
725 Waverly Route 5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. H.W. Tilley
Hotel Paumee
Merik Platte, Nebraska&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Aunt Millie,
We are in a hurry, ready to leave Topeka for Merik Platte Nebraska, Hotel Paumee. Enclosed is a letter Maifer wrote you some time ago. It is almost impossible for her to write as her vision is so bad. She can not read at all. Maifer is going to Merik Platte with me. Shall write you again when hot in such a rush to leave town. Have a four hundred mile drive ahead of us. We hope you are feeling better dear. I am awfully bust all the time. Together with caring for Maifer and this big house it is so much for me. We are all pretty well however. Hope to hear from you, maybe you know some one who will send us a card to The Paumee Htel at Merik Platte Nebraska.
Love from both of us.
Your devoted niece
Betty
(Mrs. H.W. Tilley)&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Betty Ann Tilley</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1941/06/30/from-betty-tilley-to-amelua-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 1941 16:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Betty, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1938/07/31/from-betty-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2821" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_12155771_0676.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_12155771_0676" width="2070" height="2958"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2822" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_12154839_0675.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_12154839_0675" width="2065" height="2922"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Betty Tilley, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Topeka Kansas on July 31, 1938&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Aunt Millie,
I have just finished some other writing for Mother and now I have only a few moments. I shall at least write my dear Auntie a few lines and tell you the family news.
Faye Donna, Mister Bert's oldest daughter has a lady babe, born two weeks ago. She weighed seven pounds and is just a darling. Both are doing fine. Besides Bert just ;eft, we always enjoy his Sunday morning visits. Mother is feeling fairly well, not as well as we wish she was but able to be about.
I am joining my beloved in a day or two at Les Moines, Iowa fora two weeks visit then I shall come back to mother for a month or so after then Harold and I plan a trip to eastern coast and a visit to his home in Penna. He called me over long distance last night, says he is just fine. Aunt Millie, he is a darling and I just adore him. He seems just as fond of me.
Bert is doing pretty well in his business and is happy about his grandson.
Louie as you probably knew has returned from Europe, he had a successful trip and is at present in Minnesota.
The weather is and has been very lovely so far this summer.
Mother is not as well as we wish she were but is able to be out in her car. Let us hear from you soon.
I hope this finds you and your little doggie just fine.
Lots of love from both of us,
"Hibly"
Mother says she will write you if she ever regains enough vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Hibley</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1938/07/31/from-betty-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 1938 16:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1938/05/21/from-lucy-clarkin-to-amelia-j-wiggins-3/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2795" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17292458_0646.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17292458_0646" width="1681" height="2051"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2796" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17291621_0645.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17291621_0645" width="1678" height="2024"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2797" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17294423_0650.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17294423_0650" width="1903" height="1099"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: San Diego on May 21, 1938&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Lucy C. Clarkin
2062 Venice St.
Ocean Beach
San Diego, California&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. A.J. Wiggins
725 Waverly St. K-5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. A.J. Wiggins
May 21, 1938
Dear, dear, dear, friend,
Here I am starting an air mail letter to you. We are having real May weather here now. Some fog and light showers at night. Just now the radio is reporting the crash of an air plane against a mountain top and burning, fatal to all on board.
My neighbor is laid up for repairs. She had a pretty complete Xray. She would like to have me with her all the time but I stay away when I know someone else is there.
Rheumatism and sciatica are bothering me some. Pretty painful if I do not take Iodide of Potash regularly. 1/4 of an ounce in 4 ounce of water. A tablespoon after meals is the regular dose but I take 2 teaspoons twice a day and get along pretty well.
I have not heard from Celia. She has probably joined up with her children. Maybe she and her children are probably leading regular Indian lives and living on fish and pinion nuts.
I heard a number of air planes roaring overhead during the night. Air mail week and not good weather for flying but things may be clearing up.
I am enclosing an Easter Card I mislaid and did not send.
California poppies are out in my yard, very beautiful.
My doctor and my dentist are waiting to finish my job.
I am intending to write to the grand-daughter-in-law of a 91 year old cousin of my mother an air mail letter with a dime for the old man.
Love &amp;amp; much love,
Lucy C. Clarkin
Had a severe stomach and heart attack last night. Bad indigestion.
Am sending Celia an Air Mail letter asking her to write to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Lucy C. Clarkin</category><category>Postcard</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1938/05/21/from-lucy-clarkin-to-amelia-j-wiggins-3/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 1938 23:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1938/01/18/from-lucy-clarkin-to-amelia-j-wiggins-2/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2790" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_16451077_0644.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_16451077_0644" width="1755" height="1924"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2791" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_16450271_0643.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_16450271_0643" width="1761" height="1897"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed from: San Diego, California on January 18, 1938&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Lucy Clarkin
2062 Venice Street
San Diego, California&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. A. J. Wiggins
725 Waverly St. R-5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jan. 18, 1938
My very dear friend,
Some time ago you enclosed a stamped envelope for me to answer one of your letters. I am intending to use it in sending this letter.
For several months I have not been out of my house but yesterday I went out to breakfast and lunch.
Reason: My neighbor wanted me to direct the cutting and make of a dress. She had three and one half yrs of 59 inch material. It was cut all right, now I must watch her fit and make it. She uses a 42 in pattern and then to make about 4 inch allowance.
She has a fine figure for a large woman and wont wear a dress unless she makes it fit to suit her.
She made me a present of a fine new dress for Christmas. It was a dress ordered for a wealthy woman who died before it arrived. The friendship of her and husband for me and my neighbor caused him to give it to her. It was not large enough for her but a perfect fit for me. Navy blue. I will cut a bit off of the belt and enclose it. You will see how nice it fits my butterfly pin. It takes me so long to write with the ink I have.
We have had some very nice rain. San Diego has been called Heaven on earth. Because I did not hear from Celia I did not send her the pictures you sent.
Elsie Janes lives in Beverly Hills now. She was in my Sunday School Infant Class in Columbus. Her name was Elsie Bierbower then. Such a nice little lady then and now. I am sorry this letter looks so.
Love to you always. Now do take care of yourself.
Sincerely yours lovingly,
P.S. Here is a picture of me when I was a widow the first time.
Lovingly yours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Lucy Clarkin</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1938/01/18/from-lucy-clarkin-to-amelia-j-wiggins-2/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 1938 22:50:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1937/12/06/from-lucy-clarkin-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2773" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150316_16481881_0634.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150316_16481881_0634" width="1764" height="1930"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2774" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150316_16481056_0633.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150316_16481056_0633" width="1772" height="1901"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: San Diego, California on December 6, 1937&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Lucy Clarkin
2062 Venice Street
San Diego, California&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. A.J. Wiggins
725 Waverly St.
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December 6, 1937&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My very dear friend,
I am sorry you have worried. I do not get out at all but am able to be up and cook for myself. My youngest step son brought me a fine dinner yesterday. mashed potatoes and gravy, roast beef, mixed green salad, steamed squash enough for 2 meals. I inclose a tiny hanky. Not near as pretty as one you sent me. This letter is too heavy for air mail, but you will receive it before Xmas. I am writing without glasses, second sight. Here is an Indian doctor's recipe for improving the sight. Press with the finger 12 counts at the outside of the eye, then 12 counts on the inside of the eye. The other eye too. That helps once every day to keep the eyeballs round and plump. Rubbing the eyeballs flattens the ball. Wash with cold water to strengthen.
On my first husband's marks is carved, "My son is always a gentlemen" - His mother, Dec. 7
His people were Episcopalians but he became a Catholic. Shortly after we married he was baptized. Religion was a great comfort to him. Today is a great Cardinal's birthday. He says he does love his fellow men and would gladly give his life for them.
My home a palace is
And I a queen therein
Mine is all I survey
And none may say to me nay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am in some pain still
Very truly your friend,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucy Clarkin
My niece's daughter was married Oct. 15th. Her mother sister's wedding day a Catholic wedding in Delaware.
Lucy&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Lucy Clarkin</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1937/12/06/from-lucy-clarkin-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 1937 22:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Mattie Caraher, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1937/01/01/from-mattie-caraher-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2834" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150323_12110322_0684.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150323_12110322_0684" width="2365" height="2880"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2835" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150323_12105462_0683.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150323_12105462_0683" width="2364" height="2836"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2836" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150323_12104157_0680.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150323_12104157_0680" width="1726" height="1081"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Mattie, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Kansas City, Kansas on January 1, 1937&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Amelia Wiggins
725 Waverly St.
R-#5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. J. M. Caraher
2247 Elizabeth
Kansas City, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kansas City, Kansas Jan 1-37
Dear Aunt Millie,
I read your pretty Christmas card and hope you are well. We are having lots of snow and ice. Expect you are having plenty cold weather up there. I hope you have a prosperous 1937 year. John is not able to work yet. His wrist is sore and stiff yet. He broke his wrist 3 month ago. It takes a long time to heal broken bones. Well Aunt Millie I was surprised other you are 85. I hope you have good health and hope you are not alone out there. You must take good care of yourself. So many people have colds and flu. I was in bed last week with a bad cold. Am feeling lots better now.
You wanted to know, John's full name is: John Benard Thomas Caraher.
When he was confirmed he took Thomas so you see he has 3 Saint's names.
Aunt Millie, we have told John that we are his foster parents over so don't ever mention it in your letters. We may tell him when he gets to be 21 but I don't want I'm to know yet so I know you wont mention it. Aunt Millie don;t you think you will ever get to come out here in Kansas. I expect it would be quite a big trip for me.
I haven't heard from Mabel since Christmas. They were all OK at that time.
Well Aunt Millie you write me when you can. I like to hear from you and hope you keep well.
So I will close for this time with
Love and Kisses
Lovingly your niece,
Mattie and John and Johnnie&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write soon
2247 Elizabeth Ave.
Kansas City, Kansas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Mattie Caraher</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1937/01/01/from-mattie-caraher-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1937 18:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Lucila, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1936/04/14/from-lucila-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2814" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11343699_0668.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11343699_0668" width="1498" height="2244"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2815" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11342653_0667.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11342653_0667" width="1480" height="2215"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2816" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11350406_0670.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11350406_0670" width="1496" height="2241"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2817" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11353436_0672.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11353436_0672" width="1807" height="1086"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2818" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150321_11352647_0671.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150321_11352647_0671" width="1766" height="1083"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Lucila, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Phoenix, Arizona on April 14, 1936&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;725 Waverly St. R-5&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If not called for in 30 Days
Return it to Miss Nellie
Yorks Gem Dr
Phoenix, Arizona&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix, Ariz
April 12, 1936
Mrs. Amelia J. Wiggins
Dear Mother,
As I have time I thought I would write you a few lines. Hoping my letter will find well. I am all right. How is it down there in Ohio? You You are all having some awful floods from what I seen in papers and what I been told. So I thought I would write to see if you are still alive. I hope that you dont get in those awful floods. We are beginning to have awful hot weather. I like Arizona - that is the weather here, but in summer it gets awful hot here. I feel it here more than I did any place I lived. I sure love to go back to Calif and go to Hollywood. I know all the movie stars. When is you birthday Mother? O yes have you heard anything about my kids.
Well mother I must close for this time, as I have one more letter to write. I remember the good times we used to have together. Then I got to go to town and I mail this on my way to town. I sure love to hear from my kids.
Have you every read that letter from my daughter she write to you.
Well good mother again I say good bye with love to you till I hear from you again will writte me next time.
Your daughter
Lucia&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Lucila</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1936/04/14/from-lucila-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 1936 17:35:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Lucy Clarkin</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1935/08/16/from-lucy-clarkin/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2777" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150316_17105720_0636.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150316_17105720_0636" width="2369" height="2800"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2778" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150316_17104757_0635.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150316_17104757_0635" width="2367" height="2775"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2779" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150316_17105955_0637.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150316_17105955_0637" width="2372" height="2773"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2780" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150316_17110813_0638.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150316_17110813_0638" width="2366" height="2810"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Lucy Clarkin, To: Amelia J. Wiggins
Mailed From: Ocean Beach, California on August 16, 1935&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2062 Venice St.
Ocean Beach, California&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. A.J. Wiggins
725 Waverly St. Route 5
Columbus, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug. 16, 1935
Dear, dear, friend,
I promised you a letter in a few days, but i have been very busy. Three meals a day don't get themselves. Dishes are stacked and washed once a day. Mike usually washes the. He also goes down to his son's house and washes dishes for his daughter-in-law.
She used to say to me when we were first married, 'What have you got to do? Just your little bit of housework?"
I might have asked her the same question but I just smiled. Mike has trained himself into being quite a satisfactory husband. Don't think I would ever take the job of training a husband. Both Mike and Mr. Aubury has good mothers who did quite a satisfactory job of training them.
Wright Aubury was really a saint and his mother a fine woman. She died six days before I married her son, but she wished me to marry him. I am quite sure that Admiral Reeves is a son of one of his cousins.
Wright had two cousins: Wright and Frank Reeves. Who published the Congressional Record about 65 years ago. Wright Reeves had no children and Mr. Aubury lived with him. He was a West Point man. General Grand and his wife visited the Wright Reeves family at their country home in Bladensburg.
Wright talked to him in the garden, the General asked, "Where do you come from." he answered Dutch Flats. Wright said that he thought the Gen. could not be so much because so much gold had been mined at Dutch Flats. Now I don't know myself whether Dutch Flats was in Calif. or Arizona. Tombstone used to be a thriving place. When Wright was 8 yrs. old his father and a law office there. Only one old Chinaman lives there now. Living on $4.00 a month given him by the county. Of course the Commander-in-Chief of the American Navy may be another family of Reeves but he seems to favor Wright in looks. Wright certainly honored his parents. Aug 14 was my 71st birthday. I had quite a little party. Mike's 8 year old grand daughter made her first cake for my birthday. Her mother frosted it with caramel frosting and coconut. It tasted something like butterscotch. The cake itself was light as a feather. apples, cake cookies and cocoa were the refreshments.
Mike's 2 grandchildren wanted to stay all night, but we are too old to have them here too much.
The other children brought me some little gifts, a nice little printed apron and a handkerchief and an English Language jacket. Mr. Clarkin gave me a $1.00 bill.
Do you receive the Household Magazine published by Senator Copper, Topeka, Kansas. He has been mentioned by Nuey Long as a possible candidate for the presidency in 1936. If you are not getting it you should be, as I ordered it sent to you about two weeks ago. I got the news over the radio a little while ago, that the airplanes in which Post and Roger were traveling had crashed and that both were killed. I had a hunch that this trip would prove disastrous and wished that Rogers would not go.
The government is expected to help out with old age pensions. The president has signed the bill for Uncle Sam to help out. It is said that the aged will not be obliged to sign away there bit of property under the new plan. I told you about my brother. He was in O.S.U. Hospital 17 days. He was pretty bad for awhile. The hunting season is on again in California.
There is usually a number of accidents due to carelessly handled guns.
I have thought that Celia might show up in San Diego during the Exposition. If she becomes a public charge she will probably be sent back to Chicago. her children may be as anxious to find her as she is to find them. Poor woman. Her mother was terribly sinned against. Have you ever heard David B. Bush talk over the radio. He is heard here at 9.13 AM. Success talks are his own poetry.
He tells stories of the failures and final success of successful men.
Mike likes corn bread and I make it once a week. It keeps his bowels in good condition.
I am eating home grown bananas. We let them ripen on the plant. The plant dies as the trees or rather plant dies. Mike does not care for them, but the orioles hang nests under the big levels every year.
Write soon and often.
Your Friend with Love,
Lucy Clarkin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Lucy Clarkin</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1935/08/16/from-lucy-clarkin/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 1935 23:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Betty Ann Tilley, To: Amelia J. Wiggins</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1900/01/01/from-betty-ann-tilley-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2801" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17564270_0652.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17564270_0652" width="1769" height="2536"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2802" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17571642_0654.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17571642_0654" width="1775" height="2517"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2803" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17572703_0656.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17572703_0656" width="1775" height="2529"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2804" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17573754_0658.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17573754_0658" width="1778" height="2538"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2805" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150318_17574965_0660.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150318_17574965_0660" width="1774" height="2536"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Betty Ann Tilley, To: Amelia J. Wiggins&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Aunt Millie,
I have been away from home over a month as Harold had his vacation and we spent most of the time at his home in Catarissa Penna. We drove thru and even though it was twelve hundred miles it seemed like no trip at all. Your card was forwarded to me and as always I was glad to hear from you. I had hoped to get an apt. here but we have a vacancy in one of the apts. at some and besides mother is not at all well so tomorrow Harold is taking me to Topeka and at Xmas he will come to be with us. If at all possible I shall return here at that time with him. It is very difficult for me to leave mother at all and we can not always arrange to have her with us as it is not possible for her to have her comforts any place like at "Home Sweet Home." I do hope darling you are well and have things comfortable. To be in a warm home is a lot to be thankful for, so many poor people suffer in cold weather. Speaking of weather, ever have we had such a fall even now winter has not arrived and its nearing Xmas. My little dog is sitting on the window sill looking down on the street, guess she thinks she is directing traffic as she growls when ever a dog passes or anything else she doesn't like the looks of. Aunt Millie have you tried during the past few years to get glasses? Maybe you need new ones. It's a shame for you not to have them if you could see better.
Poor mother nothing helps her any, neither the operation nor glasses and it make me very sad. She still sees enough to get around the house and neighborhood but that is about all. I miss her and her interesting letters. I am trying to write larger so you can read my letter more easily. Do you ever hear from Lela? After all the money you spent on the child its pitiful that she isn't with you when you do need her so badly. I wish it was so I could see you at least occasionally but I can scarcely leave mother to even be with my very good husband.
I received a letter from Bertie yesterday. He keeps well but so busy he hardly has time to go see mother. His two younger daughters are away to school. One in Chicago and the other in Lawrence, Ks. He sees them both often as he has to make frequent trips to Chicago.
I shall close now dearest Auntie and take my little dog out for a stroll. Again I shall say that I hope my letter finds you well and happy. Am glad you have so many good friends.
Love and a kiss,
Your devoted niece,
Betty Ann Tilley
Enclosed are a few stamps for your convenience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Entire Date Unknown</category><category>From: Betty Ann Tilley</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Amelia J. Wiggins</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1900/01/01/from-betty-ann-tilley-to-amelia-j-wiggins/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1900 00:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>