<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post Cards (Posts about To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family)</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://postcards.vdavis.net/categories/to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2022 &lt;a href="mailto:vincent@vincentdavis.net"&gt;admin&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:09:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/12/27/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-15/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2270" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16092502_0246.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16092502_0246" width="2936" height="1912"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2271" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16091584_0245.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16091584_0245" width="2909" height="1911"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2272" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16094189_0248.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16094189_0248" width="2929" height="1923"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2273" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16093266_0247.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16093266_0247" width="2899" height="1911"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2274" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16100132_0250.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16100132_0250" width="2888" height="1881"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2275" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16084540_0244.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16084540_0244" width="1517" height="1019"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2276" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/postcard-2014-20150107_16083310_0243.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150107_16083310_0243" width="1486" height="1022"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Anna Chandler Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Johnsonville, Illinois on December 27, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Return to Miss Anna Chandler
1201 South Main St.
Jacksonville, Ill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacksonville
December 26
My dearest Mama, papa, Sam, Ruby, &amp;amp; Baby Jean, Loren and dear little Audrey, Grace, Bess, Martin
The Davis Knox bless his little heart I only wish I could see him and all and see what you all got for this Christmas and wish one and all a merry christmas and a happy new year. To begin with I am glad that you thought of Barwick to send here the box of homemade candy and I wrote and told you that I wanted you to be sure and send Dr. Marselus a box of men's handkerchiefs and a neck tie cause he has been mighty good to me. He has acted as a father to me. Tell Lucerne Margaret hello for me and I thank you for what you have sent me for Christmas. I had some pop corn, candy oranges. They decorated the ward and had an entertainment and which the songs struck me - Jesus lover of my soul - it was like a funeral to me cause I thought of my folks. Tell Vinnie Virginia, Dr. Johnston and all I wish they would come and see me as Vinnie used to say dear Anna belle going to school. I only wish I could see cousin Ima Groover. Tell Ima I sure wish she could write and I sure will answer back.
Tell Sam, Loren, May &amp;amp; Dickie Robert art Uncle Wills as he is doctor also Aunt Belle Lucile Russell Kenneth. Baby oh yes you forgot to send barwick the pink scarf I ordered. Dr. Marselius said to em the other day sit down and be quiet. What do you know about that what would you think if he operated on me for adenoids as I need it done. You know that I had the goiter taken off my neck and my chin. What a scar it left when I fell down the stairs steps when I was a child and I thought I was dead sure enough the way I was cut on a hatchet. Eva Hayden is still here and she got lots of Christmas from her folks, some from Milton. Irene Heavmer is till here and she and Eva, I, I mean your little daughter Anna stick together same old girls and also Rose Sweenet has been good to me. I still wear her rings same as ever. How is Joe Maynard. Coming it tell him I said hello and be sure and write to me and tell all about the Christian Sunday School. Which I am a member and was a protege. Oh yes tell Brother Bolman he had better come and see me cause I thought of him many times and wondered where he was at. My dear little sister Edith Adeline and little brother Forest laying in the grand yard waiting for me t follow up in my fort and stone ready for me a green pond. You know that my age is 32 years and was born on the year of 1888 and my birth day is on the 21 of Oct. Tell Clifford Clarence Hanks hello as he is my cousin and also Mr. and Mrs. dr. Chad Low and sweet little Heart wouldn't I love to see her and wouldn't I love her to death and Miss Chad Low hello and all be sure and write to me. You remember I had influenza pneumonia. What a lot of sickness I have had a siege of it. How is Ruby since she had it. Has her hair come in think yet from influenza. What hospital would you like for Dr. Marselius to send me to the passionate that is the one that Ed Bolin was taken to and they sent his body back to Milton and buried and that is where my grandma grandpa and auntie and cousin Myrtle and all the rest of my folks are laid at the French yard and my Uncle Isaac Chandler buried at Phoenix, Arizona where they have a big Christina church. How is Aunt Anna David and wife and Margaret and the little fellow. John tell them to be sure and write. Poor dear old dad I sure would love to see him, Sam, Loren, Audrey, Grace, Bess, martin as he was a soldier and now telegraph operator and papa ticket agent for the C &amp;amp; A railroad. How is cousin Maynard of Okla. Tell him to write. Barwick has got some Christmas for me and be sure and send them what I told you to for Dr. Marselius. A box of mens handkerchiefs neck tie cause he sure is good to me what would I do without him. One nurse sure thinks of me after I got my Christmas bless her little heart Anna Chandler what do you know about her and Dr. Murray is another good doctor well as I have run out of anything to write and tell you about I will close and bring this letter to a final close. Hoping this find you all well and happy wishing you all a merry Christmas and a happy new year and hoping that Santa Claus has been good to one and all. I am as ever your loving little girl Anna Chandler
Pearl Ill Pike Co
In careful care
of dr marselius
jacksonville
state hospital&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Anne Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/12/27/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-15/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 1919 23:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/05/03/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-21/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1966" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_12455703_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_12455703_0002" width="2325" height="3223"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1967" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_12464044_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_12464044_0002" width="2320" height="3657"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1968" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141213_12480878_0004.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141213_12480878_0004" width="1555" height="1086"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Camp Hill, Virginia on May 3rd, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corp M.W. Chandler
Camp Hill, Va.
Cas. Set 117 Sig Br.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
Pike County&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Camp Hill, Va., May 3rd, 1919
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
Well I'm in another camp now. Was sent there from Camp Morrison. Most of the Signal Corps went to Camp Funston, Kansas. They were from Kansas City. Darn the luck--there was a bunch of fellows went to Camp Grant, Illinois yesterday, but I was billed for Texas and couldn't go with them. I went to our Company clerk and told him I wanted to go to Illinois and he said they would send me there but found out later that I would have to make request for reclassification and make affidavit that my home was in Illinois so that knocked me out of going yesterday. I made out the request as soon as I got to this camp and fixed the affidavit up but don't know just when I'll get out of here. Probably in two or three days. Sure having lovely weather. Sure wish I was home. Would like to go finishing. Bunch of men got out of here today going to North Dakota, South Dakota, Iowa, and Nebraska. As soon as they get a bunch for one state they send them out. Hope some men for Illinois gets in here soon. Sure hate to lay around this camp. I worked hard yesterday and last night on our service records getting them filled up to date so the men could get out. Worked until midnight last night. Had to make out final endorsements, fill out cards etc., am all through now. Don't feed very good here. I ate three meals in Newport News but they cost so darn much that I haven't gone down any more. That Newport News is a good deal worse than France for robbing the soldiers. A lady charged me 75 cents other day for sewing on three service chevrons. I didn't suppose it would be more than ten or fifteen cents cause it didn't take more than three minutes to do it. I told her she had just as well stand at the door with a gun and take the money as they came in. Then I went to the barber shop and got a haircut and shave and they charged me $1.25. Lord but they sure do rob a man. Frenchmen are angels compared to these robbers. Well I hope I'll soon be home. There are so many soldiers coming in here that it doesn't excite the interest of the people here at all. You'd think you were landing in some foreign country as far as the people evincing any interest in your arrival is concerned.
General Clark, adjutant General of Missouri was out to the Battalion at Camp Morrison other day and made a talk to the men. Said Kansas City was preparing a great reception for the signal corps, but of course that means the Kansas City men. They wouldn't have had any signal Corps if it hadnt been for the causals that were transferred into it. The Kansas City men proper didnt do much excel lay around at Division headquarters, most of the time away from shell fire and gas. Golly but I'll be glad to get home.
Well don't know any more to write so will close. Will wire from ou from the camp in Illinois that I'm sent to when I will leave there. Hope you are all well
Lots love to all,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/05/03/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-21/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 1919 19:42:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/03/26/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-7/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1854" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141124_12432027_0014.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141124_12432027_0014" width="3130" height="2484"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1855" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141124_12431051_0013.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141124_12431051_0013" width="3127" height="2477"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1856" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141124_12434073_0016.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141124_12434073_0016" width="3151" height="2479"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1857" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141124_12433086_0015.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141124_12433086_0015" width="3108" height="2472"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1858" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/postcard-2014-20141124_12444571_0018.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141124_12444571_0018" width="1381" height="1073"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on March 26, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corp. M.W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 H.S.C.
A.E.F.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Ill.
U.S.A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany March 26, 1919
Dearest Papa, Mama, and All
No mail since last writing. Guess I wont write very many more times from Germany . Division headquarters leaves on first train April 2nd for Brest. Rest of the division will follow and I think we will all be out of here by the 6th. Don't know how long we will lay in Brest but they say we will stay there no longer than is necessary to embark. Oh Lordy but I'll certainly be glad when I get on that ship and know that I'm really on my way home. All men are Classified here and will be sent to different camps in the States to be demobilized. I'm listed to go to Camp Bowie, Texas because I enlisted in El Paso. I tried to get it changed here but couldn't but am going to try as soon as we get to the states. I certainly don't want to go to Texas to be discharged and then have to pay carfare home. The rest of the signal camps, lot rather, those who enlisted at points in Central Miss Valley will be demobilized at Camp Taylor Kentucky. that's where I'd like to gland thats where I'm going to try and get them to send me cause then I could drop in on Lorin and Grace and it wouldn't take me long to get home from there. I rather dread the ride to Brest in Box cars but we'll be "Homeward Bound" so it won't be so bad.
Guess I forgot to enclose that speech the other day cause I found it in my pocket today. Will enclose it together with a letter from Gen. pertaining to our Commanding General.
Understand we get to keep our gas masks and helmet. I'm certainly going to bring mine home. We are going to be paid off before we leave ere but I've only got about 10/000 cummings. Had to pay for suit of underwear out of this pay. I left it somewhere or another and they charged me about 6.00 for it. They sure stick a man when he loses anything. I'll be glad to have the 10 bucks though cause we wont have much to at on the trip to Brest and that will give me a chance to buy cakes etc while going through France. They charge like the dickens in France and I expect I'll hit the states dead broke but I'll be glad to get there under any circumstances.
Everything is in readiness for the divisions departure. The general has already left for Brest. We will be deloused before boarding train at Remagen. Remagen is about 12 miles from here, on the Rhine river. We'll have to hike that distance with our packs. Pack contains 3 blankets, shirt, suit of underwear, bed sack, 3 pair of socks and reserve rations in addition to toilet articles and mess kit. Besides that have to carry rain coat, overcoat, gas mask helmet, canteen, and pistol belt. All told will weight about 100 pounds and you can imagine what it will be to walk 12 miles carrying 100 pounds. Oh well I should worry cause it will be the last time we'll have to hike any distance and so long as we're going home I don't care what we have to do just so we get there.
Just had a long talk with old pal of mine. He called me up from 2nd Division. He's still in the First Field B'n. Said he expects to stay a year. Gee but he's homesick. Says he wishes we was with me. I'm mighty glad I'm not in the regular army now.
Been having some rotten weather past 10 days. Rains or snows every day. Only a short time ago it was nice spring weather. Gee but I'll be glad to get out of this country. The German people hate to see us leave because they've received pretty good treatment at our hands.
Well I must close and go to work. Am on duty tonight at Message Center. Expect the Message Center will be one of the last details to leave here. Hope I'm in the states by time this reaches you. Will wire you when I arrive.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/03/26/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-7/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 1919 19:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family </title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/03/06/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-19/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1948" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141208_16242879_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141208_16242879_0002" width="2426" height="2943"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1949" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141208_16245131_0002.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141208_16245131_0002" width="2438" height="2968"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on March 6th, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dearest Papa, Mama, and all:
Received dandy long letter from Papa yesterday and was sure glad to get it. Have received three letters from Papa since last writing. Has been about a week since I last wrote. Also received dandy letters from Bess and Lorin yesterday. Very glad to get them. Glad every body is well now. Nothing new to write. Everything going about the same in Ahrweiler. It is again rumored that we will leave the latter part of this month but I absolutely refuse to put any faith in rumors any more. The schedule says we will leave the latter part of April. I wont believe we are going home until we are actually on our way. I mailed you a book containing cartoons of the A.E.F. this morning. They were taken from the "Stars and Stripes". They come nearer to showing things as they really were than any I've ever seen. Some of them are sure comical but guess you'd have to be acquainted with the ways of the Army before you could appreciate them. Could only get one. They seemed to be pretty scarce. They cost 5 francs--thats about a dollar. Intend to answer Lorin's letter tonight. He wrote a dandy long letter. Will answer Bess' letter tomorrow. Don't have a great deal of time to write during the day cause we are kept pretty busy but am off every night at 5 pm. Gee--we sure are having lovely weather. Regular spring. Sure makes me want to be home. Lots of our fellows have gone away to school in France and England. Some of them went to Edinburgh, Scotland. They take a four months course in what ever subject they wish. I wouldn't stay over here four months longer for all the universities in the world. Don't suppose I could get in any way.
Have been feeling just fine and dandy. Never felt better in my life. Would like to be doing some out-door work. This is too good weather to stay inside all the time. I've been to the dentist about five times during the past week. Have had two teeth filled (1 upper and 1 lower) and have two more lower teeth to be filled. My teeth haven't bothered me since Dr. Hume did the work on them at White Hall about 8 or ten years ago. The two lowers to be filled now are the ones to be filled with silver. The two lowers to be fled now are the ones he filled with silver. The silver is too prominent and makes my teeth two black so the dentist here is going to take the silver out and fill them with cement. That's only thing they fill teeth with over here. Couldn't hardly expect any thing more though, seeing that it is free of charge.
I sure hate a dentists chair. Will be glad when the work is finished. Lord-I sure wish I was home and out of the army. Bet they don't get me in the army again. I'm so sick and tired of beans and rice that I never want to see them anymore. We did, however, have biscuits for dinner yesterday. Was sure surprised. They certainly tasted good. Haven't had an egg for about 6 or 8 months. They only cost about 15 cents a piece here. Sure are scarce.
Well, will close for this time. Hope you all keep on writing. Don't see how I could get along if it wasn't for the letters I get. Hope this finds you all well. Will write again soon.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corporal Martin W. Chandler
Co. "O" 177th Field Signal Battalion,
American Expeditionary Forces.
A. P. O. 715.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Military Mentioned</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/03/06/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-19/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 1919 23:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-9/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2094" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15153571_0021.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15153571_0021" width="3264" height="1950"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2095" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15154562_0022.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15154562_0022" width="3307" height="1937"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2096" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15155345_0023.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15155345_0023" width="3280" height="1937"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2097" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141229_15160310_0024.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141229_15160310_0024" width="3301" height="1960"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on January 30, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany
30 Jan 1919
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Received letter from Papa today dated Jan 10th. Doesn't take mail very long to get here now. Certainly was glad to get it. Glad to know Ruby has recovered from the flu. First I had heard of her sickness. Sure is good to know you are all well. I'm still on the same job but expect to attend school at Coblens commencing next Monday. Cobblers is a pretty large city. Not much news about when we will leave but general impression is that we will start about the 1st of March. Certainly hope we do cause I'm mighty anxious to get home. Picked up some Radio press last night. Said 42nd and 32nd divisions would be first complete national guard units home and 77th Division would be first drafted division home. Like to get home and bid in some of there jobs that are on bulletin.
Having a show here nearly every night. Will mail you some of the programs if I can find them. Having a German grand opera tonight but I'm on duty and can't go. However they're having another one tomorrow night so guess I'll go to it. Doesn't cost anything. Have a swell theatre, looks just like the ones in the states.
Forgot to mention that I received letter from Papa other day enclosing copy of Mr. Doocy's letter. Glad you mailed them a copy of my letter. If I'm ever in Pittsfield I'll call on them.
Found out about my allotment today. it's still infect and will continue until I get out of the army.
Hope you're getting it regularly. I've been feeling just fine. Feel like I want to get out and run all the time. Have a great big feather bed to sleep in. Get lots of sleep, plenty to eat and not much work. I'll be all ready to go to work after I see you all and visit Ruby and Grace.
Think we get one months extra pay when we're discharged. That will by me a suit of clothes. It wont take me long to make enough to fit myself out with plenty of clothing. Certainly would like to get into a suit of civilian clothes again.
Rumor has it that when we leave here we sail on the Rhine up to Belgium. Sounds plausible.
Division is ranting 14 day leaves now to men who wish to visit relatives in Scotland, Ireland, England, or Italy. Guess that doesn't include me case if I have any relatives in any of those countries I don't know it. Besides I haven't the funds to provide for such a trip. Wouldn't mind going to Italy. They say Rome is a wonderful place. I'll be satisfied if they'll just send me home though. Don't think I'll ever cross the Atlantic again, once I get on the other side. Hows Knox making it? Certainly was tickled to hear about Audrey talking in her sleep and saying "God Bless her little heart." Ha ha.
I certainly did get the Christmas box and I want to say that I enjoyed it ever so much. I've a lot of back mail coming yet if it ever gets here.
Be glad when the Conference gets a peace treaty ready for Germany to sing. Hope they get things settled in Russia. See where our troops are fighting there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-9/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 1919 22:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/16/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-63/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2732" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150309_16520215_0606.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150309_16520215_0606" width="2477" height="3184"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2733" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150309_16535494_0610.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150309_16535494_0610" width="2481" height="3194"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2734" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150309_16573669_0612.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150309_16573669_0612" width="1662" height="1376"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on January 16, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corp. M.W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 F.B.S.C.
A.E.F.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany
16 January 1919
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Received two letters from Papa day before yesterday dated Dec 12 and 18th both saying Mama and Anna were sick with influenza. Sure hated to hear it. Hope they are well by now. Don't think much of that influenza.
Not much news to write. Every thing about the same as I wrote in my last letter. Am 23 years old today. Getting to be an old man -Ha. One year ago today I was in hospital at Havre, France with measles. Sure am anxious to get home. Nothing new about leaving here.
We have a YMCA and Red Cross here. Red Cross serves hot chocolate and cake every day and generally have an entertainment every night. Going to have a dance tonight from 7 pm to 9 pm. Bunch of American girls coming up from Coblenz.
Still having good weather. Suppose it is pretty cold around there now. Would like to take in some of the skating there. Guess I'll be there next winter.
Notice by Papa's letter that the girls at Wichita didn't come home for Christmas. Must have been pretty lonesome at home with everybody gone.
Well must stop and get busy. Only had time for a few lines. Hope Mama and Anna are up and around before now. Will write again soon.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corp. M.W. Chandler
C "C" 117 FBSC
A.E.F.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Envelope Included</category><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Martin Chandler's Birthday</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/16/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-63/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 1919 22:51:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/01/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-66/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2755" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150311_17111838_0626.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150311_17111838_0626" width="2451" height="2084"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2756" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150311_17110987_0625.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150311_17110987_0625" width="2423" height="2097"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2757" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150311_17113396_0627.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150311_17113396_0627" width="2441" height="2090"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2758" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150311_17114272_0628.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150311_17114272_0628" width="2461" height="2087"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on January 1, 1919&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. E.H. Chandler
Pearl, Illinois
USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany
January 1st, '19
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
Received letter from Papa yesterday and I'll say right now that I was mighty glad to get it. First mail I have received since 1st of Oct. Great to know everybody is well. Didn't know Mama was in Wichita. Sure glad to hear Ruby and child were doing well. How much does he weigh? Gee! I'm an Uncle twice now and haven't seen either one of my new relations yet but hope to before very long. We're all full of hope that we will be home by February 11th. Having very mild weather over here. Have a dandy place to stay. Nice warm fire and plenty of straw for a bed.
Just read in "Stars and Stripes" the concluding installment of the work done by A.E.F. since being in France. Written by General Pershing to Sec'y Baker. The first installment was in "Stars and Stripes" last week. It is very interesting. He doesn't give the 42nd much praise but they certainly deserve as much as any Division and more than some of the Divisions. Suppose it will be published in the Hate's so you'll have a chance to read it.
Hope the telegraphers get the raise they're after. Relay jobs and W.U. jobs should pay pretty good. Don't think I'll waste much time in going to work when I return. Haven't done much today. Just lounged around our billet. Had beef potatoes and tomatoes for dinner. Rice pudding for dessert.
I signed pay roll for 3 months pay other day. Have $120.60 coming minus 86.00 for allotments and insurance. I dont know how my allotment stands and wont find out until my service record gets back. Hope it is still going home. I made allotment 1st of Sept. 1917 good for one year. In July 1918 we had another form to sign account could only make $15.00 through government and any additional amount was to be made through Quartermaster. Don't know whether I told you of this before or not. I made $15 through QM in July 18 but don't know for how long its effective. If it was annulled 1st of September I'll get the allotment they have been charging me with, on a later pay.
We have a pretty fair shower bath here for which we are all thankful. It's a mighty hard job to keep rid of the cooties-Ha.
Well I must close. Hope I get my back mail real soon. Will write again in few days.
Lovingly,
Martin
Corp M.W.Chandler
Co "C" 117 F.B.S.C. AEF
A.P.O. 715&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1919/01/01/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-66/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 1919 23:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/12/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-59/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2684" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150227_13055568_0546.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150227_13055568_0546" width="2982" height="2432"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2685" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150227_13061331_0548.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150227_13061331_0548" width="2994" height="2457"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2686" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150227_13063229_0550.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150227_13063229_0550" width="2989" height="2454"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2687" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150227_13064938_0552.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150227_13064938_0552" width="2993" height="2461"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2688" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/postcard-2014-20150227_13070533_0554.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150227_13070533_0554" width="2987" height="2459"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: Ahrweiler, Germany on December 30, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahrweiler, Germany
Dec 30th, 1918
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Well I finally got back to my organization and consider myself extremely fortunate in getting back. Left town Christmas, hiked part of day and rode in a box car for next two days. There were 32 of us in a  car. A french box car is about half as large as ours. We were packed in like sardines. Hardly had room to sit down. Had salmon and hard tack for Christmas dinner. Expected to get my mail upon arrival here but it was all forwarded to Central post office. So guess I'll have to wait couple weeks more before getting my mail. Just my luck. Well anyway I'll get my mail regularly from now on. It's not like being in a confounded casual camp.
Germany seems a much nicer country than France. Everything is more up to date. The people all treat us very cordially but of course its for their interest to do so cause they're depending on Uncle Sam for food.
Our chief signal officer, colonel Garrett predicts that we will be in the states by middle of February. Certainly hope his prediction is correct.
Expect to go to work on Radio  job tomorrow. Have been busy last two days putting up the radio set. Have an "E-10" set. It's for both undamped and damped wave. It is only for reception. Want to get the various official "Communiques."
Our Divisional Radio set copies England, Russia, United States, and all the nearby countries. IT was made by Sergeant in "A" company. Entirely homemade.
I've had no experience whatever with an undamped wave set, my experience being confined totally to the type "A" French (Damped Wave) set - but all I have to do is receive and I know I can put down anything they send.
Having very mild weather here for this time of year. Much more pleasant than in France. Also have better places to sleep. In France we generally had a cold barn, while here we have a regular place and the German's furnish light, heat, and straw for our beds.
We have 5 hours drill each day but I wont have to do that on account being assigned to special duty.
Expect to get some mail from you all during interval of two weeks. I'm waiting for my back mail. Hope so anyway - Haven't had any mail since 1st of October. Received pay for month of September when I arrived here. They had held it. I had signed pay roll for September before leaving for hospital but wasn't paid so received it when I returned. Will get pay for October, November, and December on next pay role - that is - if they put me on pay roll. My service record was also sent away but think they have enough dope here to put me on pay role.
I don't know how my allotment stands. Made allotment Sept 1st, 1917 effective for one year and in July 1918 they brought out new form to sign. Couldn't make but $15.00 allotments through government and  any additional amount was to be made through the Quarter Master. I made $15.00 through government and $5.00 through Q.M. in July but don't know for how long it is effective. Will find out when my service record gets back. I'm being paid at same old rate so guess the allotment is still good.
Well must close for this time. Write you all again soon as I hear from you. Am feeling fine and dandy. Have gained few pounds during past month. Hope this finds you all well.
Lovingly,
martin
Corp M.W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 F.B.S.C.
AEF - APO 715&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/12/30/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-59/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 1918 20:04:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/11/07/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-61/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2717" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150307_12112675_0576.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150307_12112675_0576" width="2309" height="2782"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2718" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150307_12115075_0580.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150307_12115075_0580" width="2290" height="2786"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2719" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150307_12120780_0582.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150307_12120780_0582" width="2309" height="2804"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2720" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150307_12122035_0584.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150307_12122035_0584" width="2306" height="2791"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2721" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/postcard-2014-20150307_12123119_0586.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20150307_12123119_0586" width="2317" height="2819"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: France on November 7, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France Nov. 7th
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all
Just a few lines tonight while have plenty of time. Not much news to tell. You've all read of the papers and can see that the war is just about over. I've sure been thinking a lot about home lately and I'll be glad to get back, after being gone since December 1915. I'm leaving hospital tomorrow or next day. AM feeling great. AM very anxious to get back to my organization so can get my mail. Ought to be quite a bit waiting for me. I've written the girls at Wichita since being here also Grace and Lorin a couple of times. Haven't had any very cold weather here yet but of course its hardly time for real winter yet. You have read of the terms of Armistice signed with Austria and Turkey. Rather stringent aren't they? But no more than right though. Think thats about the same conditions that will secure peace for Germany. It practically amounts to unconditional surrender and theres no way out of it for Germany but to accept. 'Twould only be to her fault to continue the war as the Allies are in a position now to completely crush her. The Americans have been doing some very hard fighting since September. I'll never forget the Argonne Woods nor any of the other fronts as far as that goes, but north of Verdin has been the American troops hardest fights and they have shown what they can do.
Would like to get home in time to get some pickled peaches, Blackberry Jam, etc. Which I know Mama has put up. I'd like to be sitting around that base burner cracking black walnuts or eating apples tonight.
Papa how goes everything on the Cra.? Suppose though I'll find out soon as I get back to the outfit and get my mail. There'll be six letters from papa to every one from somebody else. Gee-You'll soon by 64. Wish I could be there the 24th. We'd go quail hunting sure. How's Knox getting along? Suppose he will have grown so that I'll hardly know him.
Well I must close. I'll write you just as soon as I get back to the Co. Hope you are all well.
Lovingly,
Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/11/07/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-61/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 1918 19:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</title><link>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/11/02/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-27/</link><dc:creator>admin</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2013" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09075509_0048.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09075509_0048" width="1423" height="2197"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2014" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09083048_0050.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09083048_0050" width="1448" height="2211"&gt; &lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2015" src="https://postcards.vdavis.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/postcard-2014-20141220_09085290_0052.jpg" alt="postcard-2014-20141220_09085290_0052" width="1441" height="2205"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Martin Chandler, To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family
Mailed From: France on November 2, 1918&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France Nov. 2nd '18
Dearest Papa, Mama, and all,
Thought  I'd write a few lines this pm while I had the stationary handy. Am still in hospital so have had no mail since last writing. Wont get any until I get back to my organization. I'm feeling fine and dandy and am up all the time during the day. Will be getting out before long. Notice in paper where Turkey has capitulated and it looks as though Austria will follow suit so that will leave Germany all alone. Looks as though the war was approaching the grand finale. I'd certainly love to see it over by Christmas. You've all read of the Lt. Mitice drive. Our division started that drive and went all the way through it besides holding the line for quite a while after it was over. Can't mention anything about our work since that time. Noticed that in the paper so concluded 'twas permissible for me to mention it. The allies have been doing some tall scrapping, especially the Americans. They had the hardest piece of ground to take of any of them and they're still scrapping.
Well its about supper time so must stop and peddle the coffee. I'm on K.P. here. ha. Hope you are all we'll. Don't worry any about me.
Lovingly,
Martin
Crp M. W. Chandler
Co "C" 117 FBSC - AEF&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>From: Martin Chandler</category><category>Letter</category><category>Mentions Military Service</category><category>To: Elijah H. Chandler and Family</category><guid>https://postcards.vdavis.net/posts/1918/11/02/from-martin-chandler-to-elijah-h-chandler-and-family-27/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 1918 16:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>